the most game-changing work that I've
我做过的最具变革意义的工作
ever done is
是
Marie launched a multi-million dollar
玛丽打造了一位身价数百万美元的
star of the award-winning marietv an
明星——屡获殊荣的Mar​​ietv，同时也是一位
international best-selling author
国际畅销书作家。
Marie
玛丽，请
track your time meticulously for seven
你仔细记录七天的时间，
days you will be shocked at how much
你会震惊地发现有多少
time flitters away that don't create a
时间悄然流逝，却没有
ton of value for you and you'll get an
为你创造多少价值。你会意识到，
of that if your face was stuck in
如果你的脸一直盯着
Netflix or Tick Tock for you know the
Netflix或TikTok，你永远不会想到这一点。你知道，
seven hours a day that you're not
你每天有七个小时没有在
working your book is full of solutions
工作，而你的书中充满了
to the most important challenges what
应对最重要挑战的解决方案。
are you struggling with
你正在与注意力缺陷多动障碍（
is ADHD so I can have a very overactive
ADHD）作斗争，所以我的大脑非常活跃。
brain I found myself over performing and
我发现自己过度工作，过度表现，
over working wanting to control
想要控制
everything so I could have a sense of
一切，以获得
safety that's where the real cost came
安全感。这就是我真正付出代价的地方。
in for me I started dreading waking up
我开始害怕
in the morning like I wish I could just
早上醒来，希望自己能
disappear like wow yeah see these were
消失。哇，是的，这些
scary thoughts and it almost destroyed
想法很可怕，几乎毁了
my relationship
我的感情。
in the book you took about these three
你在书中提到了支撑
rules that underpin this figure outable
这种解决问题的
mindset yes and it's just helped me in
思维模式的三条原则，是的，它帮助了我生活的
every different facet my relationships
方方面面。 人际关系、
my mental health my business what are
我的心理健康、我的事业，
those so rule number one is that
这些是什么？第一条规则是……
rule number two
第二条规则……第三条规则
that's super important Point number
非常重要……
three it's the one we don't talk about
第三点，也是我们不谈论的一点，
you have to be willing to just
你必须愿意……在
before this conversation starts I've got
对话开始之前，我想
a favor to ask from you 74 of people
请你帮个忙。
that watch this podcast frequently
经常收听这个播客的人中，有74%
haven't yet hit the Subscribe button and
还没有点击“订阅”按钮，
nine percent of people haven't yet hit
9%的人还没有点击“
the Bell to turn notifications on the
铃铛”开启通知。
bigger this platform gets the bigger the
这个平台越发展壮大，
guests get so if you could do me one
嘉宾的影响力就越大。所以，
favor if you've ever enjoyed this
如果你喜欢这个
podcast please hit the Subscribe button
播客，请帮我一个忙，点击“订阅”按钮
and turn notifications on without
并开启通知。
further Ado I'm Stephen Butler and this
废话不多说，我是斯蒂芬·巴特勒，这里
is the Diary of a CEO I hope nobody's
是《CEO日记》。我希望没人
listening but if you are then please
听到，但如果你听到了，请你
keep this yourself
保密。
[Music]
[音乐]
Murray
默里
when I was reading your book you talk
我在读你的书时，你谈到
experience is one of the things that
经验是
ends up shaping the beliefs we have in
塑造我们对世界信念的因素之一。在
what were the experiences that you had
你
at the very earliest of Ages that end up
很小的时候，有哪些经历最终
shaping the beliefs you've had about the
塑造了你对世界的信念？其中一个
one of the biggest ones was actually a
最重要的经历实际上是
memory I had when I was about seven or
我小时候的一段记忆。 我大概七
eight years old
八岁的时候，
so my parents had just gotten a divorce
父母刚离婚。
and I remember being in the kitchen in
我记得当时在
my house in New Jersey with my mom and
新泽西的家里，
I'm looking at her and she has one of
我和妈妈在厨房里。她拿着一部
the old school phones with the cord like
老式电话，电话线缠在
wrapped around her hand and it was
她手上，
wrapped around so tight that her hand
缠得那么紧，手都快
was kind of turning white because she
发白了，血液
was cutting off the circulation
循环都受阻了。
and she was on the phone with her mother
她当时正在和在佛罗里达的妈妈打电话，哭得
was crying unconsolably
泣不成声。
and I'm watching my mom with tears
我看着妈妈，泪水
running down her face and her everything
顺着脸颊流下来，整个人都憔悴不堪。
looked drawn and she was saying
她说：“
I have nothing I have nothing do you
我什么都没有，我什么都没有，你
understand I have nothing I don't know
明白吗？我什么都没有，我不知道该
what I'm going to do and so you know
怎么办。” 你知道，她泪流满面，我吓得
Frozen in fear
动弹不得。
he hangs up the phone and she bends down
她挂断电话，弯下腰，
and I just see like her makeup running
我看到她的妆都花了，
down her face and the tears running down
泪水顺着
her face and she puts her hands on my
脸颊流下来。她把手放在我的
shoulders and she puts her face right
肩膀上，把脸凑到我
next to mine up to my nose and she
脸边，几乎贴着我的鼻子，
shakes me
摇晃着我，
and she says do you see what I'm going
说：“你看看我
through right now
现在有多痛苦，
I have nothing do not be stupid like I
我什么都没有，别傻了。” 就像我当时说的，
was don't ever let a man don't ever let
永远不要让男人，永远不要让
anyone control your money I need you to
任何人控制你的钱。我需要你
grow up I need you to be your own woman
长大，你需要成为你自己的女人，
I need you to be independent don't be
你需要独立，不要像
stupid like me
我
and Stephen I was just like you know as
和斯蒂芬那样傻。你知道，我当时才
a seven or eight year old like in shock
七八岁，震惊不已。
of course I love my dad my dad's an
当然，我爱我的爸爸，他是个
amazing man and I love my mom and that
很棒的人，我也爱我的妈妈。那段
experience like in a few seconds I made
经历就像在短短几秒钟内，我
all of these equations in my mind and I
在脑海里做了很多计算，做出了很多
made all these decisions and I made all
决定，也
these promises to myself and I'll tell
对自己许下了很多承诺。我告诉
you what those were
你，其中
one of the decisions was that
一个决定是，
the lack of having enough money equaled
缺钱就等于
the loss of love
失去爱，
the destruction of family and so much
家庭破裂，以及巨大的
pain and suffering like seeing my mom in
痛苦和折磨。比如看到妈妈
pain knowing my dad wasn't there knowing
痛苦，知道爸爸不在身边，知道
my family using unit wasn't okay and I
我的家庭状况不好，我
just everything felt unsafe and I made
感觉一切都不安全。
this promise in this decision I said
在这个决定中，我许下了一个承诺：
okay when I grow up
等我长大后，
I'm gonna somehow make so much money
我一定要赚很多钱，
that I am going to take care of the
照顾
people I love and if anyone around me
我爱的人。如果我身边有人
needs money to to handle the pain I'm
需要钱来应对痛苦，我一定会
going to be able to take care of them
帮助他们。
now looking back I'm in my 40s now I can
现在回想起来， 我现在四十多岁了，我
see how much that fear and how much that
意识到，那种恐惧和
desire to have love be healed has driven
渴望治愈爱情的愿望，
almost every part of my career
几乎驱动着我职业生涯的方方面面。是的，
to have love be healed yes what do you
你这话是什么意思？
because I had this notion that because
因为我以前一直觉得，
my parents love was broken
父母的爱情破裂是因为家里没钱。
when we are driven by insecurities
当我们被不安全感驱使时，事情
it can be it can get a little bit out of
可能会失控。
hand yeah you know when something like
你知道，当
that like money becomes your North Star
金钱成为你的北极星时，
it almost means that the other stars are
其他的“星星”——那些
form our very human needs what was the
构成我们基本人性需求的东西——几乎都会黯然失色。那么，把
money as a motivator in some ways it was
金钱作为动力，其代价是什么呢？从某种程度上来说，这
wonderful because it was there was a
很棒，因为它培养了我
rooting in solid work ethic that was
扎实的工作伦理，这很棒；
fabulous and at the same time a
但同时，它也是一种
self-punishment
自我惩罚：
I'm never doing enough
我永远做得不够好，还不够，
it's not quite enough this is not good
这还不够好，
enough it can be better I can be better
我可以做得更好。
and you know for many years especially
你知道，很多年，尤其是
early in my career I didn't really have
在我职业生涯的早期，我根本没有
an off button you know it was working
休息的时间，
seven days a week morning until night
一周七天，从早到晚都在工作，
um you know missing out on whether it
错过了很多…… 可能
was friends getting married or this one
是朋友结婚，或者这个朋友、
or that one and some of that you know
那个朋友结婚，你知道，
it's complicated it's multi-layered
这很复杂，牵涉到很多方面。
right A lot of times if friends were
很多时候，比如朋友们要去
to Vegas or whatever I legitimately
拉斯维加斯参加单身派对什么的，我真的
didn't have the money to go and I found
没钱去。我发现
myself working all the time just to kind
自己一直在工作，只是为了
of climb out of debt in the early days
在创业初期还清债务。
of my business for example so there's a
所以，这里面
little bit of give and take there you
有点得失，你
know there's the cost and I think
知道，是有代价的。我觉得
eventually as I started to get into my
最终，当我到了
40s I started recognizing just this
40岁左右的时候，我开始意识到自己过度表现、过度付出、过度努力的
pattern of over performance of overdoing
模式。
of over pushing sometimes I would say to
有时候我会跟
my partner Josh we've been together for
我的伴侣乔希说，我们在一起
like 20 years and I would say God you
20年了，我会说，天哪，你
know I really want to take a break right
知道吗，我现在真的很想休息一下，
now but I've got X Y and Z to do and I
但我还有X、Y、Z等事情要做。我
said I don't I just I feel so lazy if I
说，我不想休息，我只是觉得如果休息的话，我感觉自己太懒了，根本
take a break I can't take a break like
休息不了，事情
there's so much and he's like Marie you
太多了。他会说，玛丽，你
were one of the most productive non-lazy
是我这辈子见过的最有效率、最不懒的人之一。
matter how many times he said that to me
无论斯蒂芬跟我说过多少遍，
for so long I didn't believe him
我一直都不相信他，
I was like he's lying he he's not as
我觉得他在撒谎，他不如我
productive as I am he has lower
高效，他的
standards than I do which is all not
标准比我低，但这都不是
true
真的。
um and it was uh it was tough it was it
嗯，这很艰难，他
was just I wasn't very kind to me
对自己不太友好。
how do you how do you balance that
你该如何平衡这一切呢？
because on one end you know the feeling
一方面，你知道，不满足的感觉
motivating absolutely it means that
确实能激励人，这意味着
you're always striving you're pushing
你一直在努力，不断鞭策
people you're you know there's always
他人，你知道，总有
more work to be done you're always at
更多的工作要做，你
the one percent in your pro in your
的项目总是进展到百分之一。
projects but on the other hand
但另一方面，
um it's also for many a deferral of
对很多人来说，这也意味着将
their happiness and contentment off into
幸福和满足感推迟到
the future somewhere that will keep
未来某个地方，随着他们的
moving as they move yeah off into the
前进而不断变化，最终到达
distance yep how where is The Sweet Spot
遥远的地方。是的，那么，如何在
between knowing there's more work to be
知道还有更多工作
done but also being content at the
要做和享受当下之间找到平衡点呢？是的，
moment yes I love this a I think for me
我喜欢这个。我认为对我来说，
it is this ever evolving daily practice
这是一个不断发展的日常练习，
that I never quite get right but I'm
我从未完全掌握，但我一直在
always playing with
尝试。
these days it's about recognizing that
这些天，关键在于认识到……
you know what I have created so much I'm
你知道我创造了这么多，我为
so proud of what I have and I'm a human
我所拥有的一切感到无比自豪。我是一个有
that is entrepreneurial and
创业精神、
multi-passionate and creative so there's
充满热情和创造力的人，所以，
all these things it's the joy of going
所有这些特质都让我感到无比喜悦，
like oh my goodness I'm so grateful for
就像“天哪，我太感激我所
what I have and here are the things that
拥有的一切了”，同时我也对即将
I am so excited to create and for me it
创造的东西充满热情。对我来说，这
becomes this really beautiful Dynamic
形成了一种非常美好的动态状态，
sense of being where I am fully joyful
我完全沉浸在喜悦
and grateful for exactly what's
和感激之中，感激正在
happening and super excited for what I'm
发生的一切，也对
creating next so in the past it was like
接下来要创造的东西感到无比兴奋。过去，我总是觉得“
oh well this isn't good enough I'm not
哦，这还不够好，我不够
good enough I don't have you know it was
好，我没有”，你知道，这种想法源于一种
coming from a place of lack where these
匮乏感。而现在，我的想法源于
days I'm coming from a place of
一种
contentment and then an additional place
满足感，以及
of curiosity and excitement about what's
对未来即将发生的事情的好奇和兴奋。你明白我的意思吗？
of course it does yeah how many people
当然明白。
do you think you've coached over the
你觉得过去一年你指导过多少人？天哪，
oh my goodness I think that would depend
我想这取决于
on your definition of coached so we've
你对“指导”的定义。
we've had over 100 million people
我们有超过1亿人
interact with our our videos and given
与我们的视频互动并提供了
advice you've heard your advice or your
建议。 听过你的建议或
words
话语吗？有没有那么
was there a moment when you realized
一刻，你意识到
that this is what you wanted to do with
这就是你想要的
your life yes because I know you went to
人生？是的，因为我知道你在
Wall Street longer than you oh my
华尔街待的时间比你长得多。哦，
goodness I failed at so many jobs so
天哪，我做过很多失败的工作。
um I remember when I was on Wall Street
嗯，我记得我在
on the New York Stock Exchange I was
纽约证券交易所的华尔街工作时，我真的很
really excited about it because it was
兴奋，因为那里蕴藏着
this place where there was tremendous
巨大的
potential for income right and I was
收入潜力。我
around people that were making millions
身边的人年收入数百万
of dollars a year which is so far beyond
美元，这远远超出了
anything I could have imagined in my
我当时的想象。
life at that time and I was I kept
但我内心深处一直有个
hearing this little voice inside Stephen
声音在说：“这
I was like this isn't who you are this
不是你，这不是你应该
isn't what you're meant to do this isn't
做的，这不是
who you're supposed to be and that
你应该成为的人。”那个
little voice kept getting louder and
声音越来越大，
louder but the little voice didn't tell
但它没有告诉
me what else I was supposed to do and
我我应该做什么。有
one day I was crying my eyes out because
一天，我哭得泣不成声，因为
I felt like such a failure my parents
我觉得自己太失败了。我的父母为了让
had busted their buns to help me get
我上
through college first in my family to go
大学付出了巨大的努力，我们家第一个上大学的人。
to school and I knew that I was so lucky
我知道我能
to have that job just any job right
找到那份工作是多么幸运，哪怕只是一份工作，一份
Healthcare a steady paycheck and here I
医疗保健行业的工作，一份稳定的薪水。而我却……
was miserable I wanted to quit so bad
我当时痛苦极了，特别想辞职，
and I just felt trapped because I didn't
感觉自己被困住了，因为我不想
want to bring shame upon my family I
让家里蒙羞，
felt like a total failure and the little
觉得自己彻底失败了。
voice then said call your dad so I took
这时，一个声音告诉我给爸爸打电话，于是我
out my flip phone at the time which
掏出了当时的翻盖手机——
gives you an idea it was like the lay
你可以想象一下，那是
late 90s and I was crying to my dad and
90年代末的年代——我哭着给爸爸打电话，
I said Dad I'm so sorry like you and Mom
我说：“爸爸，对不起，你和妈妈为了
worked so hard to get me through school
供我读书那么辛苦，
and and I just I can't stand this job I
我真的受不了这份工作，我
want to quit and he broke in all my
想辞职。”他打断了我抽泣的
sniffly snotty crying and he's like Ray
哭声，说：“雷，
he's like calm down he's like if this
冷静点，如果这份
job is getting you this sick and you
工作让你这么难受，这么
hate it you have to quit I said but Dad
讨厌它，你就必须辞职。”我说：“可是爸爸，
I don't know what I'm supposed to do
我不知道我该怎么办，
like this isn't like me and he said look
这不像我。”他说：“听着，
you're going to work for the next 40 or
你接下来的四五
50 years of your life you have got to
十年都要工作，你必须
find something you love and if this job
找到自己热爱的事情。如果这份工作
isn't it then start bartending do
不是你想要的，那就去做调酒师，去做
whatever you need to do again but don't
任何你需要做的事情，但不要
stop looking until you find something
放弃寻找，直到找到
that you really really want to go to do
你真正热爱的事情。” 我
every single day
每天都想做自己想做的
so the only things I knew about myself
事，所以我对自己的了解仅限于
were that I loved business but I was
我热爱商业，而且我
also highly creative and the only com
极富创造力。当时唯一让我觉得能
in an industry was magazine publishing
在这个行业里有所作为的，就是杂志出版业，那还是个热门行业。
at the time that was still a thing and I
于是我
went to a temp agency I got a job at
去了一家临时工中介，在《美食家》杂志社找到了一份工作。
Gourmet magazine but about six months
但大约六个月
into that job which was interesting I
后，有趣的是，我
started hearing that same voice against
开始听到那个反对
Stephen I was like Ugh this isn't who
我的声音。我心想：唉，这不是
you are this isn't what you're supposed
你，这不是你应该
to do this isn't what you're supposed to
做的，这不是你应该
be so I'm on the internet one day at
成为的人。有一天
work probably when I shouldn't have been
上班的时候，我可能不应该上网，但我还是上网了。
and I stumbled upon this new profession
我偶然发现了当时一个叫做“教练”的新兴职业。
when I read this article it was as
当我读到这篇文章时，感觉就像
though something in my soul lit up like
我灵魂深处有什么东西像圣诞树一样亮了起来，就像云开
parted and little angels came out and I
雾散，小天使们走了出来。我
was like oh like this is what you're
心想：哦，原来这就是我
supposed to do and I said I'm gonna do
应该做的！我说我要去做
this life coaching business and I went
人生教练，于是我又
back to bartending and waiting tables
回去当调酒师和服务员，全身心投入
and just devoted myself to figuring out
到研究
how to build a business during the day
如何建立自己的事业中。
okay so let's go back through so the
好的，我们回顾一下。所以，内心的
voice inside yes what is that voice
声音，对我来说，那是什么声音？
to me I believe it is my intuition
我相信那是我的直觉，是
it is my when I say higher self I
我所说的“高我”，我
believe the part of me that is timeless
相信那是我永恒的一面，它
that's probably been here before and
可能以前就存在过，而且在
that will be here Beyond this particular
这次
incarnation
轮回之后也会存在。
and if anyone out there I certainly do
如果有人相信
believes in a higher power that there
更高的力量，我相信还有
are other levels of intelligence that
其他层次的智慧在
are actually supportive of us that's who
支持着我们，那就是
I think that voice is does everyone have
我认为的那个声音。每个人都有
that voice I absolutely believe so
那个声音吗？我绝对相信。这是
that's my personal belief everyone has
我的个人信念，每个人都有
that voice they may not have been
那个声音。他们可能没有接受过
trained
训练
to articulate and understand and discern
去表达、理解和辨别
it but I believe it's there what does it
它，但我相信它就在那里。它是什么
feel and sound like
感觉，听起来像什么？
soft spoken
轻声细语。
it feels as though you're having an
感觉就像你内心被轻轻
inner nudge towards something that may
推着，朝着某个方向前进，这个方向
not make sense to the outside world it
在外人看来可能毫无意义，它
may be counter to all of the social
可能与你从小接受的所有社会和
conditioning the familial conditioning
家庭观念相悖，
that you've been brought up with but it
但它
is gentle it is encouraging and it is
是温柔的，是鼓励的，也是
persistent I thought you were going to
坚持的。我还以为你会
say persistent that's the last word I
说“坚持”，这是最后一个词，
was like because I I can I can relate
因为我能感同身受。
um
嗯，
why is it that and it's funny because I
为什么会这样呢？这很有趣，因为 我
also agree that everyone has that voice
也同意每个人都有这种声音，
um because when I have conversations
因为当我
with people they will often tell me who
与人交谈时，他们经常会告诉我他们是谁，做什么工作。
they are and what they do yeah and then
然后，
this the second thing is they'll like
第二点是，他们会突然
whip out their phone and be like and
拿出手机，说：“
I've got this art Instagram account and
我有个艺术Instagram账号。”
I'm like all the other voices like
我心想，其他的声音就像
infiltrated the the Asylum and it's like
入侵了避难所，有点儿
taking over a little bit like I love
占据了我的内心。比如，我喜欢
doing I work in the city I work in
在
finance but check out my art over here
金融行业工作，但看看我的艺术作品吧。这就像是
it's kind of like the whisper that yes
耳语，没错，这就是
thing inside you that's been
你内心深处的声音，它一直在
persistently working away at you it made
不断地影响着你，让
you at 2AM launched that Instagram
你在凌晨两点创建了那个Instagram
account
账号。
um but most people because of the
但是，大多数人因为
there's another voice at play which is
另一个声音的存在，也就是
the external voice Society your mother
外部的声音——社会、你的母亲、
your parents your immigrant parents
你的父母、你的移民父母，
telling you what work is Instagram
告诉你什么是工作，Instagram
telling you what you should and
告诉你你应该做什么，
shouldn't be an R
不应该做什么。
um that other voice that external Voice
那个外部的声音
is so much stronger yeah it's so much
要强大得多，它
stronger and it's everywhere it's in all
无处不在，存在于
of our friends it's in our parents it's
我们所有的朋友中，存在于我们的父母中，它无处不在。 对，没错。那么，
up down left right yes how does one go
我们该如何
taking the perceived quote-unquote risk
承担所谓的“风险”，去
of tuning into the that voice that's
倾听那轻声细语的声音呢？
just Whispering yes oh I love this
哦，我喜欢这个
question and I also love talking about
问题，也喜欢谈论
this because I think it is one of the
这个话题，因为我认为它是我们每个人都拥有的
most powerful sources of wisdom that we
最强大的智慧来源之一。
that we can talk about I want to talk
我们可以谈论的话题有很多，我想谈谈其中
about a few one is if you start to pay
几个。其中一个就是，如果你开始
attention to the small things so I'll
关注一些小事，我举个
give you an example
例子。
I've actually been practicing this is
我一直在练习这个，这听起来可能
going to sound extremely superficial but
很肤浅，但请听
stick with me intuitive shopping I don't
我细细道来——直觉购物。我不
like to own a lot of things I'm just not
喜欢拥有很多东西，我不是那种
a person who likes a lot of clutter and
喜欢杂乱无章的人，
I just don't want to have a bunch of
我也不想家里堆满
crap lying around and so I realize that
乱七八糟的东西。所以我意识到，
sometimes I'm like oh well so and so if
有时候我会想，哦，好吧，比如
I try on an outfit or whatever I'm like
我试穿一套衣服，我会想，
oh I think this looks pretty good and
哦，我觉得这件看起来不错。
I've been paying attention to like nope
我之前一直在注意，比如“不，
you're never gonna wear it it sounds so
你永远不会穿它”，这听起来
silly but when I quiet down and I listen
很傻，但当我安静下来，倾听内心的声音时，
I'm like okay I have this little
我会想，好吧，我在
guidance for these little moments of my
这些小时刻得到了一些指引。 我
day on the best path to take I want
每天都想找到最佳的人生道路，我希望
people to pay attention to the small
人们关注生活中的小细节，比如
moments what you should order on a menu
菜单上该点什么菜，
whether or not you should make a move
或者是否应该
with your partner if people actually
对伴侣采取更进一步的行动。如果人们
look back in time and start to look in
回顾过去，审视
their past you'll see places where you
自己的经历，就会发现曾经有过这样的时刻：你
heard that little voice and you overrode
听到内心的声音，却压抑了
it and you got yourself into trouble
它，结果让自己陷入了困境。
do you know those times of course so
你当然有过这样的经历。
everyone has usually if you start to
通常每个人都有过，如果你仔细想想，
filter through your mind it could have
这可能是
been a financial decision it could have
一个财务决定，
been a business decision it could have
一个商业决定，一个
been about someone to hire it could have
关于招聘的问题，也可能是
about saying yes to a job a relationship
关于接受一份工作或一段感情的问题。总有一些
but there were times when something in
时候，
you was piping up and your ego or an
你内心深处的声音在作祟，你的自尊心或者某种
external voice was like no you got to go
外部的声音告诉你：不，你必须接受
for this this is a great deal this is
这个，这笔交易很划算，它能给
going to get you X Y and Z you should
你带来X、Y和Z，你应该
say yes to this and you overwrote that
答应它。然而，你压抑了内心的
little voice and it cost you big time so
声音，结果付出了惨痛的代价。所以，要
I think to answer the question how do
回答“
people start to kind of hone into that
人们如何才能培养这种
discernment I think look in your past to
辨别力”这个问题，我认为应该回顾过去，看看
where you ignored it before and you'll
你曾经忽略过它的地方，你会
have examples of like oh that's what it
找到一些例子，比如：哦，
sounds like that's what it feels like
听起来是这样，就是这样。 感觉
that's one and then I think number two
这是第一点，然后我觉得第二点也
this works for me I'm someone who has
对我有用。我患有注意力缺陷多动障碍（
ADHD so I can have a very overactive
ADHD），所以我的大脑非常活跃。
brain I need to meditate and I need to
我需要冥想和
exercise those are two things that help
锻炼，这两件事能帮助
me dial down the noise so much of the
我减少噪音，消除很多杂音，
static and create enough space for that
为内心的声音创造足够的空间。这样我
inner voice to not only feel like for me
不仅能更容易地
to be able to detect it more but for it
察觉到它，还能让它更
to speak louder and for me to hear it
清晰地表达出来，让我能够听到它。
one of the things that sometimes
有时候，
encourages us or
我们会被内心的声音所左右，甚至
wins in US overriding The Voice
战胜它。那个
that small Whispering inside you telling
在你内心低语的声音告诉
you who you are what you should be doing
你，你是谁，你应该做什么，你应该在
where you should be what you're capable
哪里，你能够做到什么。而这些声音往往源于
of is our own like fear insecurities and
我们自身的恐惧、不安全感和
Trauma so like I can think of multiple
创伤。比如，我可以想到很多
times where I've made bad decisions
次，我因为过度受不安全感的影响而做出了错误的决定。
insecurities you know whether it's money
无论是金钱方面的
decisions whether it's love decisions
决定，还是爱情方面的决定，
typically anything that's like psycho
通常任何
psychological in its root so money food
根源上与心理有关的事情，比如金钱、食物
these kinds of things so you might know
等等。你可能知道，
and even in the context of a
即使在
professional career
职业生涯中，
having the upbringing that you've had
你的成长经历也会影响你对金钱和食物的认知。
where you made that Association super
很
early that money results in a loss of
早就有人认为金钱会导致失去
Love or the lack of money results in a
爱，或者缺钱会导致
loss of Love or a loss of control or
失去爱，或者失去控制
whatever that can orientate you to go to
等等，这些都可能让你涌向
Wall Street yes as opposed to listening
华尔街，而不是倾听内心的
to The Voice yep how much do we have to
声音。是的，我们需要
like heal in order to to kind of turn up
疗愈多少才能放大内心的声音，
the volume of that voice inside and to
并
try and turn down the external voice you
试图降低外界的声音呢？
know it's a great question I think we're
这是一个很好的问题。我认为我们都
all on a healing Journey constantly
在不断疗愈的旅程中，
because I think all of us you know we've
因为我们每个人都
kind of collected little hurts
积累了一些小的伤痛、
disappointments
失望，以及
um things from our childhood things from
童年和
our adult experiences that kind of get
成年经历中的一些事情，这些都深深地烙印在我们的记忆里。
lodged in there I don't necessarily know
我不确定
requires like hearing your intuition
倾听直觉是否需要
requires you to heal anything because I
疗愈什么，因为我
think that voice is always trying to
认为内心的声音一直在试图与
talk to you and I think one of the best
你对话。我认为
ways to understand it's your intuition
理解直觉的最佳方式之一就是倾听你的直觉，
and not fear and we should maybe talk
而不是恐惧。我们或许应该稍微谈谈
about that a little bit that's a I can
这一点。我可以
give people a very simple exercise about
给大家一个非常简单的练习，教大家
how to know is this my intuition
如何分辨这是我的直觉在
speaking up saying no you know like you
告诉你“不”，比如你
shouldn't go in this direction or is
不应该朝这个方向走，还是
this just fear because I want to stay
仅仅是…… 害怕是因为我想保持
safe and I don't want to put my ass on
安全，不想冒险。
here's how I tell it so let's say I'm
我是这样描述的：假设我正在
thinking about saying yes to a
考虑是否接受某个
particular opportunity it could be a
机会，可能是一笔
business deal it could be you know
生意，也可能是在
speaking at a particular event anything
某个活动上演讲，诸如此类。
When I close my eyes and just feel in my
当我闭上眼睛，感受我的
body and say does the idea of saying yes
身体，问自己：接受
to this make me feel expansive or
这个机会让我感到舒展还是收缩？
contracted and Stephen when I ask that
斯蒂芬，当我问自己这个
question in a nanosecond I say okay does
问题时，我会在瞬间问：
saying yes to the speaking engagement
接受演讲邀请让我感到舒展还是收缩？
feel expansive or contracted I guarantee
我保证，
in your body you feel something it is so
你的身体会有所感觉，非常
subtle but either there is a lightness
微妙。
there is like your body starts to expand
要么你会感到轻松，身体开始舒展，身体向
like this you lean forward there could
前倾，甚至
be a little bit of Joy even if you're
会有一丝喜悦。即使你吓得魂飞魄散，即使你觉得接受
this is like oh my goodness it's the
这个机会是
biggest opportunity ever or your ego
千载难逢的良机，或者你的自尊心
wants to say yes but inside there's a
想要答应，但内心深处却有一个声音在
part of you that says no it closes down
说“不”，它让
you feel heavy you feel a sense of dread
你感到沉重，感到恐惧。
that's your intuition trying to lead you
这就是你的直觉在试图引导你走向
in the right direction question yes do
正确的方向。问题是：
you ever do things that are contractive
你是否曾经做过类似的事情？ 那种
in feeling oh my gosh not as much
感觉很压抑，天哪，现在好多了，
anymore but I did it so often earlier on
但我在早期经常这样，
my journey because I was so desperate
因为我太渴望得到
for approval people and I was so
别人的认可，太渴望
desperate to be successful and I had
成功了。我当时的
these ideas if I partner with this
想法是，如果我和这个
person if I say yes to this particular
人合作，如果我答应参加这个
activity if I show up here then I'm
活动，如果我出现在这里，我的
gonna have some kind of more stature
地位就会更高一些。
right or I'm gonna be noticed more so
对，或者说我会更引人注目。
these days it happens much less
最近这种情况发生的频率低了很多，
frequently and I feel like that just
我觉得这大概是因为我磕磕绊绊、
enough and tortured myself enough and
自虐过度、
created enough pain and Chaos that I'm
制造了太多痛苦和混乱，所以我觉得
like I don't need to do that anymore
我不需要再那样做了。是的，
yeah because a lot of the time the
因为很多时候，
reason I asked that particular question
我问这个问题的原因
is a lot of time a lot of the time
是，很多时候，都会有
there's a short term
短期的
carrot I think that's the analogy for
诱惑。我想这就是个比喻，
yes it's a short-term carrot which goes
没错，就是短期的诱惑，比如“
listen we'll give you this if you come
听着，如果你来做这件事，我们就给你这个”。
and do this thing you don't know if I
我不知道自己能不能
can do it but the short-term carrot can
做到，但短期的诱惑
be tempting sometimes the long-term
有时很诱人。长期
effects of taking a short-term carrot
吃短期的诱惑
are dangerous the other question I had
是危险的。我还有另一个问题，是
which was thinking about this expansive
关于这种扩张
contractive thing is there has been
收缩的。有时候，
times where something has made me feel
某些事情会让我感到
contractive yep but when then I've gone
收缩，是的，但当我去做之后，天哪，
oh my God you're so glad that you did so
你真庆幸自己做了，真庆幸自己做了。
glad I did it I'm curious when you felt
我很好奇你是什么时候感到
contracted and then you overrode that
收缩，然后又克服了这种感觉的。
can you tell me more about whether it
你能详细说说，是不是因为听到了什么
was the voice like what made you
声音吗？ 是什么让你
override that feeling
克服了那种感觉？
um money interesting you're going to get
嗯，钱，有意思，你
paid loads of money to go and do this
要去那里做这件事，还能赚一大笔钱。
thing I think oh [__] I don't want to
我想，哦，天哪，我不想
travel yeah I don't want to go there and
旅行，是的，我不想去那里
do it but then you go there and you have
做这件事。但是，当你到了那里，和别人进行了一次
a great conversation for example if I'm
很棒的对话，比如，如果我在某个地方
speaking somewhere sure and I and it
演讲，当然，这让我很兴奋，这就是让
lights me up that's what lights me up
我兴奋的原因，是的。
yes so I walk away from it feeling
所以我离开的时候感觉
unbelievable thanks I'm so happy I did
难以置信，谢谢，我很高兴
I'm so happy I did that yeah
我做了这件事，这真的改变了我的心情，让我和人们建立了联系，我很高兴我做了这件事，是的。
um but ahead of time you know it's funny
但是，你知道，这很有趣，
because it's the story I'm telling
因为是我
myself ahead of time that's making me
事先给自己编的故事让我
feel contractive it's I'm telling myself
感到沮丧，是我对
about travel about time Wasted by having
旅行的想象，关于
to go to another country or city or
去另一个国家、城市或
place I'm thinking about all the time
地方浪费的时间，我想着所有
wasted okay and the money for me Isn't a
浪费的时间，好吧，对我来说，钱并不是一个
real big motivator but it almost for me
很大的动力，但对我来说，
it's like it's still hard to turn down a
拒绝一大笔钱仍然很难，
big number sure because the money
当然，因为钱。 它
doesn't come to me it supports the team
不是针对我个人的，它支持团队，
it supports this podcast it supports our
支持这个播客，支持我们的
show we have we this in my personal team
节目。我们拥有这个，在我的个人团队里，
we have 25 20 people now yeah so a lot
我们现在有25到20个人。是的，所以很多人的
of livelihoods I think of it as a
生计都依赖于此。我认为它是一种
response ability yes so let's play here
响应能力。是的，所以我们在这里玩
for a moment because I think that's so
一会儿，因为我觉得
interesting what you shared a lot of
你分享的内容很有意思。
what you felt dread about was thoughts I
你感到恐惧的很多事情都是想法，我想知道，
wonder and this would be fun maybe you
这会很有趣。也许你
can text me and let me know in the
可以发短信告诉我，
future I'm curious more of a body
以后我会更感兴趣。我更感兴趣的是一种身体
sensation right right so like you I can
感觉，对吧？对吧？就像你一样，我可能会想，
be like oh boy got some travel coming up
哦，天哪，马上要旅行了，
and my thoughts can generate a sense of
我的想法会产生一种
tiredness let's say but what I'm when
疲惫感，比如说。但是，当
I'm talking about expansive and
我谈到扩张和
contracted I'm actually talking more
收缩时，我实际上更多的是在谈论
about a physical sensation in your body
你身体里的一种物理感觉，就像
almost like either in your solar plexus
在你的太阳神经丛
or in your gut so it's less of a thought
或你的腹部一样。所以它与其说是一种想法
generated feeling and more of a visceral
产生的感觉，不如说是一种发自内心的
full body notion does that distinction
全身感受。这种区别是吗？是的，
yeah yeah just I'm I'm super curious
我只是非常好奇，
because I agree with what you've said in
因为我同意你所说的，
terms of there's been times where I'm
有时候我也会这样想。
like oh I don't know about this and I
哦，我不太清楚，我当时……
was so and I got over myself I was like
我克服了自己的想法，心想，
you know what there's X Y and Z people I
你知道吗，那里有我喜欢的X、Y和Z，
like them there I'm gonna go see them
我要去见见他们。
and I was so happy that that I wasn't a
我很高兴自己没有固执地
stick in the mud and stayed home so I
待在家里，所以我也
had that experience too I'm
有过类似的经历。
I want to dive a little deeper with you
我想和你更深入地探讨一下
on that body sensation because in my
那种身体感觉，因为以我的
experience that's usually where the
经验来看，直觉通常就存在于身体之中，
less thought generated more body more
少一些思考，多一些身体感受，多一些
body truth the body holds the school
身体的真理。身体承载着一切。是的，是的，那我们再回顾一下。
so we're talking about this journey that
我们正在谈论
led you to leave the publishing industry
你离开出版业，
yes and decide to go back to being a
决定重操旧业做
waitress but also pursuing the career of
服务员，同时又追求
being a coach yes a couple of key things
教练事业的这段旅程。是的，这里有一些关键点
there that are that we kind of glossed
我们一带而过。
over that are I know people are sat at
我知道很多人坐在
home thinking they're in jobs they hate
家里，觉得自己做着讨厌的工作，身处讨厌的
they're in situations they hate they
境地，他们
hear the voice they get it
听到了内心的声音，他们明白了。
the next part I guess there's two parts
接下来我想说的是两部分。
there the next part is
接下来是，
how do I how do I
我该如何
tune into the voice and and like how do
倾听内心的声音？还有，我该如何……
um
嗯，
you were lucky in the sense that you
你很幸运。 你
read that article yes I say lucky but
读到那篇文章的感觉，是的，我说幸运，但
maybe that's not the best use of words
也许你用词不太恰当。
you have you read that article that came
你读到那篇文章，它恰好出现在
to you at that time that's right maybe
你的脑海中，没错，也许是
the universe sent it to you the
宇宙把它送到你面前的。
Journey's out right
旅程结束了，对吧？
if I know I'm in the wrong place and the
如果我知道自己身处错误的地方，而内心有个
voice is saying [__] Steve this magazine
声音在说“去他妈的史蒂夫，这家杂志
publishing is not right yeah but I don't
出版公司不对”，是的，但我不
know where the right place is how does
知道正确的地方在哪里。
one go about finding that right place
一个人该如何找到正确的地方呢？
okay I love this question so here's a
好吧，我喜欢这个问题。这里有一句
mantra and I live my life by Montrose
箴言，我奉行蒙特罗斯的人生格言，
they help keep me on track and here's
它帮助我保持正轨。还有
one that really works Clarity comes from
一句真的有效的箴言：清晰源于
engagement not thought Clarity comes
参与，而非思考。清晰
from engagement not thought what does
源于参与，而非思考。
that mean in this context it means that
在这个语境下，这意味着什么呢？这意味着，
every single person listening right now
现在正在收听的每个人，
let's say they have a job and they're
假设他们有一份工作，他们想：“
like I am done with this job but I don't
我已经厌倦了这份工作，但我不
know what else I should be doing there's
知道接下来该做什么。”
something in them that has an interest
他们内心深处肯定有某种兴趣，
it could be an interest in art it could
可能是对艺术的兴趣，可能
be an interest in baking it could be an
是对烘焙的兴趣，也可能是对
interest in music find a way to go take
音乐的兴趣。找到一种方法，朝着
action in that direction no matter what
那个方向行动，无论
it is it could be interning for someone
是什么，哪怕是去实习。
working for them for free picking up a
免费为他们工作、拿起一本
book taking a class finding some way to
书、参加课程，想方设法参与到
get involved in that area will give you
那个领域中来，
not only Insight but it'll start to open
不仅能让你获得洞察力，还能
up creative channels you'll start to
开启你的创意渠道。你会开始
meet people you'll start are to say oh
结识新朋友，你会开始说：“哦，
this is great as a hobby but I would
这作为爱好很棒，但我
never want to do this as a career I
绝不会把它作为职业。” 我
think that all of the Insight Clarity
认为所有的洞察力和清晰的思路都
comes from engagement not thought you're
来自于参与，而不是思考。你
not going to figure it out sitting on
不可能坐在
your couch you're not going to figure it
沙发上就找到答案，也不可能
out necessarily scrolling on Instagram
刷着Instagram
or your phone you're gonna figure it out
或手机就找到答案。你需要采取
by getting into some kind of action and
行动，允许自己去尝试，
right giving yourself permission to try
允许自己去尝试，也许会
things and it might not work and that's
失败，但这没关系。
okay but you're going to learn something
你会学到一些东西，你会
you're going to discover something
发现一些东西，
you're going to have a conversation
你会与人交流，你会偶然发现一篇属于
you'll stumble upon your own article
你自己的文章，你会感觉
where your own body lights up like a
自己像
Christmas tree and you'll be like oh my
圣诞树一样闪闪发光，你会想：“哦，我的
goodness this is the thing but it's not
天哪，就是它了！” 但
going to come if you sit at your desk
如果你每天坐在办公桌前，
every day know that your work isn't
明知自己的工作
right but you don't do anything active
不对，却不采取任何
to actually go find out what is but you
实际行动，灵感就不会出现。 去弄清楚到底是什么，但你
know I'm busy I've got four kids I've
知道我很忙，我有四个孩子，我
got a job I just don't have the time
还有工作，我就是没时间，对吧？
right oh that's uh not having the time
哦，没时间
is probably one of the biggest excuses
可能是
that we can all use from time to time
我们时不时会用到的最大借口之一，
and it really is an excuse because all
而且它确实是个借口，因为
of us know when it's important enough we
我们都知道，如果事情足够重要，我们会挤出时间；
make the time if not we make an excuse
否则，我们就会找借口。
we know this if you're spending any
我们都知道这一点。如果你把
amount of time on Instagram or tick tock
时间花在Instagram或
on social if you listen to podcasts if
社交媒体上，如果你听播客，如果
you do anything outside of your actual
你做任何工作之外的事情，除了吃饭、
job and just feeding yourself and doing
吃饭和做你为了
stay alive you have time you really do
生存必须做的事情之外，你其实是有时间的，真的有。
you have to do some basic math I would
你得做一些简单的数学计算。我
recommend we talk about this in the book
建议我们在书中讨论一下，
is track your time meticulously for
仔细记录你
seven days you will be shocked at how
七天的时间。你会惊讶地发现，有
much time flitters away doing things
多少时间在你做的事情上悄悄溜走了，这些事情并
that don't really create a ton of value
没有为你创造多少价值，
opportunity to even have open time where
甚至没有给你任何自由时间，让
you're not looking you're not consuming
你不去看、不吸收
anything where you're not having other
任何东西、不被
people's thoughts ideas or agendas
别人的想法、观点或计划所影响。 把这些想法
inject into your head where you're just
注入你的脑海，
giving yourself time to walk around the
给自己一些时间在户外走走，在
outside and take a walk in the block and
街区里散散步，亲近
in nature and actually let your mind
自然，让你的思绪自由驰骋，放松身心，
think or wonder or rest or exercise or
或者
do any of these other things that can
做些其他能
open creative channels where you'll get
打开创意通道的事情，让你获得
a download and you'll get an idea of
灵感，产生一些想法，比如“
like oh my God I would have never
天哪，
thought of that if your face was stuck
如果你的脸一天七小时都盯着
in Netflix or Hulu or Tick Tock for you
Netflix、Hulu或者TikTok，我永远也想不到这个”。好吧，
not working fine I'm quitting my job I'm
我要辞职了，我要辞职了。辞职
quitting quitting is difficult yeah
很难，是啊，这有
what's scary why is it so how do we
什么可怕的？为什么这么可怕？我们该如何才能
better quitters I was on stage this
更好地放弃？我今天
morning I sat on stage and I said it all
早上在台上，坐在台上，我一直在说，
the time so it's like I sound like a
所以我听起来像个
broken record but you know we glamorized
复读机。你知道，我们把
starting it's like oh my God they
开始美化了，好像“天哪，他们
started this thing but quitting is the
开始了这一切”，但放弃和开始
equally important thing you have to do
一样重要，是的，
before you start yes and so quitting is
所以放弃和
just as much of a skill as starting
开始一样，都是需要技巧的。
anything how do I become a better
我该如何才能更好地
quitter I look at your journey continue
放弃？看看你的经历，不断地
quitting yeah throughout and it's funny
放弃，是的，贯穿始终。这很有趣，
because that almost sounds like an
因为…… 听起来几乎像是在
insult doesn't it no yeah but it does on
侮辱人，不是吗？没错，但
the surface because quitting is for
表面上确实如此，因为放弃是
losers yes well if you believe that
失败者的行为。是的，如果你相信这一点，那
that's the that's the slogan right but
就是口号，对吧？但
if you hadn't quit imagine the the
如果你不放弃，想想你会多么
misery I would have been so miserable
痛苦，我会非常痛苦。
and so I think there's a couple of
所以我认为这里面包含两点：首先，
things to it one I think understanding
我认为了解
your risk averseness as a human being is
自己作为一个人的风险厌恶程度
very important and let me tell you what
非常重要。让我告诉你这对
that means for me financially speaking
我的财务状况意味着什么。
I'm fairly risk averse so because of my
我相当厌恶风险，因为我的
upbringing because of this kind of
成长经历，以及那种
Perpetual Financial scarcity that there
持续的财务匮乏，
was I'm not the kind of person who's
我不是那种会
just going to burn the ships behind me
破釜沉舟、放弃杂志社工作，然后开始做
start this coaching business and figure
教练事业、摸索前行的人。
it out it was like no I went back to
不，我又回去当
bartending and waiting tables pretty
调酒师和服务员，
much seven days a week because that's
几乎一周七天都工作，因为只有这样才能
what it took to keep the roof over my
维持生计，才能让我有地方住，才能让我
head and eating food while I figured out
有饭吃，同时我才能摸索出我的
this life coaching business so I would
人生教练事业。所以，我想
say for anyone listening right now if
对正在收听的任何人说，如果
you're thinking about quitting take a
你正在想…… 关于辞职，不妨
look inside what's your risk averseness
审视一下你的内心，看看你的风险承受能力如何。
you know there's a study that was done
你知道吗？美国有一项研究
in the United States they tracked about
追踪了大约
14 000 entrepreneurs and they found that
14000名创业者，发现
those who kept their day job as they
那些在创业初期保留日常工作的人，
less likely to fail
失败的可能性降低了33%。
and so I think for anyone listening it's
所以，我想对于所有听众来说，这就像是在问：
like okay well you may quit this job but
好吧，你或许会辞掉这份工作，但你
is there any other circumstance whether
还有其他什么情况吗？
part-time like what is going to be the
比如，你找了另一份工作，或者转为兼职？你需要什么
kind of financial Runway or situation
样的财务缓冲期，或者说
that you need to give yourself an
你需要什么样的情况，才能让自己有
ability to see if this business could
能力判断这项事业是否可行？
work if starting a business is what you
如果创业真的是你
want to do
想做的事，那么
and and so after you quit
在你辞职后的
um seven years
七年里，你一直在
doing side work yes and growing and
做兼职，也在不断发展和
figuring out the business
完善你的事业。
for your coaching business if I'd ask
如果我当时问你，你对你的教练事业有什么期望？
you on that day I'm going to say you
我会说，那是
know how long ago was that so that was
多久以前的事了？那是2000年，大概是2000年到
two thousand like 2000 2001. right so
2001年吧。对，
that's 20 odd years ago if I'd asked you
那是20多年前的事了。如果我当时问你，
where are you going to end up oh my
你打算做什么？ 结果，我的
goodness I had no freaking clue I at
天哪，我当时完全不知道该怎么办。
that moment I was just entrenched in my
我当时一心扑在
coach training and I wanted to be a
教练培训上，一心想成为一名
great coach so badly meaning I didn't
优秀的教练，这意味着我并没有
really have a huge Vision because
一个远大的愿景，因为
everything was so new and I think there
一切都太新鲜了，充满了不
was so much uncertainty and quite
确定性。
frankly as a 23 24 year old I didn't
坦白说，作为一个23、24岁的年轻人，我
really have the ability to have Vision
根本没有能力去构想未来。我
like I read so many success books
读过很多成功学书籍，
Stephen that were like you know and this
斯蒂芬，你知道，在
was like kind of a line in many of the
很多我参加的人脉
networking talks I'd go to it's like
拓展讲座中，都会有人问：“
well what's your five-year Vision right
你的五年愿景是什么？”
I was like I have no idea I'm literally
我当时想的是，我完全不知道。我当时一心
trying to just get the next three paying
只想找到接下来的三个付费
clients like I will Coach your dog if
客户，比如“如果你愿意，我甚至可以指导你的狗”。
you let me I will Coach that's where I
我当时就是这种状态，
was because I was so committed to trying
因为我一心想
to be the best coach I could be and I
成为最好的教练，我
knew that I needed experience I needed
知道我需要经验，需要
to work with as many people as possible
尽可能多地与人合作。
so I had no vision for where this thing
所以我对未来没有任何规划，
would go I just kept taking the next
只是不断地迈出下一步，再下一步，再下一步，就这样一步一步地走下去。这种现象很少有人
and kind doing this it's not talked
提及。
about enough what you've just said
你刚才说，
because perfectionism is one of the
完美主义是
things that causes procrastination and
导致拖延的原因之一，
especially as we set out to quit and
尤其是在我们准备放弃旧事物、
start the new thing you hear it all the
开始新事物的时候。
time I know you do which is well I
我知道你肯定经常听到这种说法：这个我
haven't got enough of this and I haven't
还没做够，
figured out this and I need to find a
那个我还没搞清楚，我需要找个
mentor and an investor and this and a
导师、一个投资人，还有这个、一个
website name and this and that whereas
网站名字等等。但
in reality in everything I've ever done
实际上，我做过的所有事情都是这样，
it's this like horrifically messy
一团糟，跌跌撞撞地摸索
stumbling forward in into the darkness
前进，就像在黑暗中摸索一样。就连
like and even with this podcast like
这个播客也是这样，
I'll tell you how it came to be was I
我来告诉你它是怎么诞生的：我
enjoyed doing it that was it that was
喜欢做播客，仅此而已，这就是我的想法。我
the thesis didn't know how we'd make
不知道怎么
money didn't know how big it would get
赚钱，不知道它会发展到多大，也不
didn't know if other people would like
知道其他人会不会喜欢。
it actually still blown away that anyone
事实上，直到现在，我仍然对有人
listens because it's like it's been one
收听感到难以置信，因为这简直是世界上最棒、最鼓舞人心的事情之一，
things that people care about the types
人们竟然关心
of conversations we have here yes but I
我们在这里进行的对话。是的，我
think that's such an important message
认为这是一个非常重要的信息，
because perfectionism as you write about
因为正如你
in the book you talk about progress and
在书中写到的，你谈到了进步和
perfectionism and which one to choose
完美主义之间的关系。 选择哪一个，这简直太
it's such a it's such an imprisoning
让人纠结了，这种
notion that is so pumped up by like fake
想法被那些假
life coaches and fake entrepreneurs that
人生导师和假企业家们无限放大，他们想方设法向
want to try and sell you something to
你推销东西，把
make them by making themselves seem like
自己包装成
they are super special and God gifted
超级特殊、天赋异禀的人。
yes we're all just messy little
不，我们都一样，杂乱无章、胆小
unorganized scared
怕事，
um 100
百分之百都是
and so human and so this is the other
普通人。所以，还有一点，那就是在
thing like so start before you're ready
你准备好之前就开始。
so Stephen I have to tell like as a
斯蒂芬，我得告诉你，作为一个
young life coach I knew how ridiculous
年轻的人生导师，我知道
it all sounded it sounded cheesy to me
这一切听起来多么荒谬，多么俗气。再说一遍，
again can I tell you my first Workshop
我的第一个工作坊只有
there was five people in it I was 24.
五个人，我当时24岁。
that's a lot my parents
这已经很多了，我的父母、
my yoga instructor from college and
我大学的瑜伽老师，还有
um one of her neighbors actually two of
她的一个邻居，实际上是两个
her neighbors that she pulled in off of
邻居，她从
the street and I had created a whole
街上拉过来的。我用
Microsoft clip art I stapled the little
微软的剪贴画做了一整本小册子，把这些小册子订
workbooks together and I stood in front
在一起，然后站在
of five people in my yoga teachers
我瑜伽老师在
basement in New Jersey and I delivered
新泽西的地下室里，对着五个人讲了一
like a day-long workshop and like I
整天的工作坊。
think back to that cringy Marie but she
回想起那个尴尬的玛丽…… 但她
was also awesome because she started
也很棒，因为她在还没
before she was ready she didn't know
准备好的时候就开始了，她完全不知道
what the hell was going on but she did
发生了什么，但她还是做了。
it and it was like the worst thing I
这可能是我做过的最糟糕的事，
probably ever did but I did it and then
但我还是做了，然后
it gave me a little bit of experience to
它给了我一些经验，让我可以
then like go do something else and then
去做其他事，然后再
go do something else so to your point
去做别的事。所以就像你说的，
it's like everything for me has been
对我来说，一切都
messy I'm like I don't know if this is
乱糟糟的。我会想，我不知道这会不会
gonna work this sounds like a lot of fun
成功，这听起来很有趣，
I have energy towards it I want to make
我对此充满热情，我想
a difference let's try it
有所作为，那就试试吧。那
and what about today as you sit here now
你现在坐在这里的时候呢？嗯，
um today it's still messy I've talked
今天仍然很混乱。我一直在说
about this all the time I'm like you
这一点，你
know 99 of what any of us need to do to
知道，我们每个人为了
grow our business we've never done
发展自己的事业需要做的事情中，99%都是我们以前从未做过的，
before so we don't know what the hell
所以我们根本不知道自己在
we're doing that's why for me everything
做什么。这就是为什么对我来说，一切都是可以解决的。
is figureoutable this phrase is so
这句话非常
useful like I use it every day still
有用，我每天都在用它。但这
it's not like there's some blueprint or
并不意味着有什么蓝图或
some road map to guaranteed success out
路线图可以保证成功，事情
there like that's not how it works and
不是这样的。
if you're someone who's Innovative or
如果你是那种…… 创新、
creative or you're trying to do
创造，或者你想做一些与众不同的事情，
something outside of the box there
那
certainly ain't no Playbook so you have
肯定没有现成的剧本可循，所以你必须
to be willing to just try things and
愿意尝试、
experiment and flop around and laugh at
实验、摸索、自嘲，
yourself and then get up the next day
然后第二天重新振作，继续尝试。
and do it again in the book you talk
你在书中谈到了
about these the three points of
这三个
philosophy that oh the three rules the
哲学要点，哦，这三个规则，是的，这
three rules yeah the underpin this
三个规则支撑着这种
figure outable
可解决的思维模式。
mindset yes what are those so rule
那么，它们是什么呢？
number one is that all problems or
第一条规则是，所有的问题或
dreams are figureoutable rule number two
梦想都是可以解决的。第二条规则是，
if a problem or a dream isn't figure
如果一个问题或梦想无法解决，
outable it's a law of nature right so
那就是自然规律，对吧？比如
death maybe taxes rule number three you
死亡，或者税收。第三条规则是，你
may not care enough to solve a
可能不够在意去实现某个
particular dream or reach a particular
特定的梦想或达成某个特定的
goal and that's okay find something that
目标，这也没关系。找到
you do care deeply about and go back to
你真正关心的事情，然后回到
rule number one and what that does is it
第一条规则。这样做的好处是，它为
a container for us as human beings to be
我们人类创造了一个容器，让我们
honest about what we care enough about
诚实地面对我们真正关心并愿意去
to go figure it out because in in my
解决的事情。因为在我的
life there hasn't been one thing yet
人生中，还没有哪件事是
that I have truly wanted to either
我真正想要
understand achieve transform do you know
理解、实现或改变的。你知道吗？
what I have some different relationship
我对它有一种不同的感觉，只有
with that when it was true in my heart
当我发自内心地想要…… 我一直
that I haven't been able to figure it
没能
out and if I don't want to figure
弄明白，如果我不想弄明白
something out like I can get real at
某件事，比如，我可以坦诚地告诉
myself like I don't care enough about
自己，我根本不在乎
this to go figure it out right now
这件事，所以现在没必要去弄明白。
that's super important yes number three
这一点非常重要。是的，第三点，也是
it's the one we don't talk about yeah
我们很少谈及的一点。
because we'll all have goals in our life
因为我们每个人的人生中都会有一些
that we
我们
we think are important we think we want
认为重要的目标，一些我们认为自己想要实现的目标。比如，
to do I want to you know I want to
我想
become a DJ I want to start working out
成为一名DJ，我想开始健身练出
and get a six-pack I want to be an
六块腹肌，我想成为一名
artist
艺术家。但这些目标
they they often don't happen and we we
往往无法实现，我们
end up thinking that they haven't
最终会认为它们没有
happened because we are an unmotivated
实现是因为我们缺乏
person so we say you know we start being
动力。所以我们会说，你知道，我们会开始
ourselves up I'm not motivate I'm a
自我否定，说我没有动力，我是个
failure I'll just keep trying at it we
失败者，但我还是会继续努力。我们
very rarely pause and go do I actually
很少停下来问问自己：我真的
want to and there's this weird thing
想要吗？我注意到一件很奇怪的事情，
that I that I noticed which I won't name
我不会点名道
the person but they know who they are
姓，但他们知道我说的是谁，
because I know they're listening there's
因为我知道他们在听。
this weird thing that I observed which
我观察到一件很奇怪的事情，它
taught me a really important lesson is
教会了我一个非常重要的道理：
sometimes like we want to want something
有时候，我们想要拥有某样东西，但实际上并非如此。
and the way we're just laughing the way
我们只是在笑，
that I describe that is like
我描述的方式就像
we want to want something we want to
我们想要渴望某样东西，我们想要
have the motivation to do the thing we
有动力去做我们想做的事，我们
want to want it yeah we want to want it
想要它，是的，我们想要它，
we think we should want it yes so we so
我们认为我们应该想要它，是的，所以
we go around saying we want it so like I
我们到处说我们想要它，比如，我
wanna I really want to go and lift
想，我真的想去
weights I might say Stephen I really
举重，我可能会说，斯蒂芬，我真的
want you know I I'm saying to the world
想要，你知道，我是在告诉全世界，
you know I really want to go and lift
你知道，我真的想去
weights but it's because I want to be
举重，但那是因为我想成为那种想要成为那样的
the type of person that wants to be that
人，是的，
that wants that yes so I go around
所以我到处
saying it but I don't actually want it I
说，但我实际上并不想要它，我
just want to want it yes I had this same
只是想想要它，是的，我和
conversation with my best friend and we
我最好的朋友也聊过
were laughing about this because I have
这个，我们都笑了，因为在我的职业生涯中，我给
put so much pressure on myself at so
自己施加了太多的压力，
because I think I should want something
因为我认为我应该想要某些东西，是的，然后
yeah and I'm like but if I okay for
我就想，但是如果我，好吧，举个
example I think you'll appreciate this
例子，我想你会理解的，
because I think you and I share a
因为我认为你和我有着
similar philosophy perhaps um about
相似的理念，比如，关于
social media for example
社交媒体，
so I suck at social media right I'm
所以我不擅长社交媒体，对吧，我从来不用
never on it I don't put any attention
它，我不关注它，
and I actually had a colleague of mine
实际上我有一个同事 有人
say to me like Marie you're so good at
跟我说，玛丽，你这么擅长
what you do like why aren't your numbers
你做的事，为什么你的粉丝数量不多？
bigger and it was like one of these you
你
know like when someone makes a comment
知道，就像有人评论你，
you're like oh that kind of feels like a
你会觉得“哦，这感觉就像被人狠狠打了一拳”，然后
punch in the gut and you're just like oh
你会想“哦，
oh I I don't know and anyone who knows
哦，我不知道”。任何了解
me my friends and even my audience they
我的人，我的朋友，甚至我的观众，他们都知道
know I'm like very transparent like I
我很坦诚，我
don't spend a lot of time on my phone
不怎么玩手机，
like I'd prefer to write books I create
我更喜欢写书、开发
programs like there's other things and
程序，还有其他的事情要做。
then I I just want to live my life like
我只想好好生活。
I feel like I'm like oh there's like oh
我感觉自己好像在想，“哦，
if I was really committed to being a
如果我真的想成为一个
change maker then I would be making
变革者，那我应该做
videos I was like what the hell is that
视频才对。”我当时想，这到底是什么鬼
philosophy like I remember torturing
想法？我记得我曾经折磨
myself I should want to want that
自己，我应该渴望那样做，
exactly but the truth is I don't exactly
但事实是，我并不渴望。
and that's the hard part to admit yes
承认这一点很难，是的，
yes it's a really hard part to admit
承认
that we just don't care enough we just
我们不够在乎，我们就是不想，那是
don't want it it's someone else's it's
别人的事，那是
someone else's and I think that just
别人的事，真的很难。 我觉得我们刚才的
having this conversation because I would
对话很有意义，因为我
imagine there's folks listening to us
猜想现在正在听我们说话的有些人
right right now that think that they
觉得自己
should want to want something and they
应该渴望某样东西，但他们并
don't and then what happens so you know
没有。然后会发生什么呢？比如，
I failed to go to the gym to get that
我没能去健身房练出
six-pack that I I tell myself I want or
我一直告诉自己想要的六块腹肌；或者
I failed to start that business because
我没能创办那家公司，因为
I don't really want to but I want to
我其实并不想，但我又很想
want to start it yeah and then I use
开始。然后我就开始找
excuses I and the the number one excuse
借口，最常见的借口
is I just don't I don't have the time
就是“我没时间”。
because that's a cloaking of as you said
正如你
earlier that's a cloaking of your true
之前所说，这其实是在掩盖你真正的
priorities yep it's a way of saying so
优先事项。没错，这其实是在说“这不是
it's not my fault it's just a lack of uh
我的错，只是
time in the day there's only 24 hours
时间不够用，一天只有24小时”。
but really as you've said it's actually
但正如你所说，
that the how you use your time as one of
你如何利用时间，恰恰最能
the clearest demonstrations of your
体现你的
actual priorities of your values yeah
价值观和优先事项。 嗯，
100 100 the the way that I always like
100% 100% 我一直喜欢对
to keep myself honest about like what I
自己诚实，清楚自己
want and to call myself out on my own
想要什么，并且会毫不留情地指出自己的
excuses this is the the two-word
借口。正是这两个词的
distinction that has helped me the most
区别帮助我
understanding the difference between
理解了“
can't versus won't so any time that I'm
不能”和“不愿”之间的差异。所以，每当我
about to say oh I can't do that I can't
准备说“哦，我做不到”、“我做不到”、“我没时间
do this I can't get up earlier to work
早起锻炼练出
out to get those six packs I can't can't
六块腹肌”、“我
write my next book I just don't have the
写不了下一本书”、“我没
time for me learning Italian I can't
时间学意大利语”、“我
learn Italian I have so much on my plate
学不了意大利语”、“我
right now with my business so 99 not 100
现在生意太忙了”的时候，99%（不是100%）的
99 of the time when we human beings say
时候，我们人类说“
can't it's a euphemism firm won't and
不能”其实是一种委婉的说法，更确切地说是“不愿”。而“
what does won't mean won't means we
不愿”的意思是，我们
really don't want to we're not willing
真的不想做，我们不愿意
to make the sacrifice it's not that
做出牺牲，这件事
important to us right now and so I
现在对我们来说并不那么重要。所以我
always encourage myself and other people
总是鼓励自己和其他人
to play with this like any time you're
尝试用这个概念，比如，每当你
about to say the word can't try on won't
准备说“不能”的时候，不妨先试试…… 不会，
or try on that's not a priority for me
或者说尝试一下，这对我来说现在不是优先事项。
right now and see how your body feels
看看你的身体感觉如何，
going back to this body truth something
回到这种身体的真实感受。我内心深处会想，
of me goes you know what I actually
你知道吗？我其实
don't want to learn Italian right now
现在不想学意大利语。
you know why because in my free time I'm
你知道为什么吗？因为我的空闲时间都在
watching the house of dragons I do you
看《龙之屋》，你
know what I mean I'm watching this show
知道我的意思吗？我在看这个节目，
or that show or I'm hanging out with my
或者那个节目，或者和
friends or I'm doing this I'm doing
朋友们出去玩，或者做
something else where I could be
其他事情。我本来可以把
dedicating that to my Italian Studies
这些时间用来学习意大利语，
but I'm not you know why because that is
但我没有。你知道为什么吗？因为这
not my priority right now that is so so
不是我现在的优先事项。这更加
much more honest and it's so much more
坦诚，也更加
freeing and then all of a sudden I'm not
自由。然后突然间，我不再是
a bad person I'm not not ambitious
一个坏人，不再是一个没有抱负的人，
enough I'm just me it's so it's so such
我就是我。这是一个多么
a small important change in like words
微小却重要的改变，就像改变措辞
and and thinking just that swap swap
和思维方式一样。
from I can't do something which says
从“我做不到”——这表示
it's not possible right or I'm not in
不可能，对吧？或者从“我无法
control which is even the worst one I
控制”——这甚至是最糟糕的——变成“
can't it's not not possible to I won't
我不会”。这会以一种非常
which empowers you in such an important
重要的
way it says actually these are decisions
方式赋予你力量。它表明…… 实际上，这些都是
that I'm making I'm not the puppet I'm
我自己做的决定。我不是傀儡，我是
the puppet master of my life that's
自己人生的幕后操纵者，没错，
right and I get to call the shots around
我可以在
here that's right and it says I and I
这里发号施令，没错。上面写着“我”，我
think just like that's not my priority
觉得，就像现在这不是我的首要任务，
right now I choose not to that's not my
我选择不那样做，这不是我现在的
choice at this it's not much better you
选择。其实也好不到哪去，你
can try on any one of those but all of a
可以试试这些方法，但突然之间，你内心深处似乎
feels the honesty you feel the alignment
感受到了某种真诚，感受到了某种和谐，我们
all of us you feel more alive and you
所有人都会感到更加鲜活，
have more energy and I'll tell you you
更有活力。我告诉你，只要你足够多地这样
do that enough you tell yourself the
做，足够多地对自己说
truth about you enough and all of a
实话，
sudden you start falling in love with
突然之间，你就会开始爱上
the real you
真正的自己，而
not the you that you think you're
不是你为了取悦他人而认为自己
supposed to be to get everyone else to
应该成为的那个自己，
like you not the you that Society has
也不是社会
told you that you have to be or all the
告诉你必须成为的那个自己，或者所有
people that you compare yourself to who
你用来比较的那些人——他们
are probably faking it anyway but you
可能本来就在伪装自己。你会
fall in love with the real you and
爱上真正的自己。以
that's in my experience where real
我的经验来看，真正的
happiness and satisfaction and
幸福、满足和
fulfillment comes from
成就感就来自于此。
from
从“
I can't to I won't is in the external
我不能”到“我不会”的转变，就在于此。
because I made the mistake with my
我曾经犯过一个错误，那就是和我的
partner once upon a time of when she
伴侣之间建立外部关系。当时她
suggested something to me and I did not
建议我做某件事，而我不想
want to do it I would say I can't right
做，我会说“我不能”。其实
what I'm doing is I'm absolutely lying
我完全是在撒谎，
to her because she you know she she
因为她
wants to go and do this thing at this
想去某个地方做这件事，
place and I guess I can't because I
但我因为时间安排满了，所以去不了。
what I'm doing is I'm is I'm telling her
我告诉她我
I want to so ask me again in the future
很想去，以后再问我吧，
because I'm interested
因为我对这件事很感兴趣，
but I can't right now because of an
但现在因为一些
external Factor so my girlfriend keeps
外部因素去不了。所以我的女朋友一直
asking me if I want to do this thing and
问我愿不愿意做这件事，而
I'm continuing to continue to say I
我一直说“
can't and it's building a really
不行”。这建立在一段非常
inauthentic relationship well that's
不真诚的关系之上，而这段关系
fundamentally built on a set of Lies
本质上是建立在谎言之上的。有
there was a point and I think it was
一次，我想是
because one of my podcast guests where I
因为我的一个播客嘉宾，我
just tried being honest yeah and it was
尝试坦诚相待，那是
the best thing I've ever done yeah and
我做过的最好的事情。
you know what she really appreciated it
你知道吗，她真的很感激，
because I don't want to do that it's so
因为我不想那样做。坦诚非常
important even you know in business and
重要，无论是在商业、
in relationships and all of those things
人际关系还是其他任何方面。
someone being honest with you is very
有人对你坦诚相待非常
rare that it's so effective when they
难得，但一旦坦诚，效果却出奇的好。
are I actually took a phone call as I
我当时正
was coming down the stairs to start this
下楼准备开始这段
conversation from someone and they
对话，突然接到一个电话，对方
called me and said
说：“嗨，
hi Stephen just so you know this is a
斯蒂芬，先跟你说一声，这是个
cold call so if you if you um don't want
推销电话，如果你不想
to do the chord just hang up now but if
接，现在就挂断。但如果你
you've got 20 seconds let me know
有20秒钟的时间，请告诉我。”
and I was shocked
我当时真的震惊了，
absolutely shocked the guy probably I
非常震惊。那人大概是跟我
think he told me he listened and I said
说的，他听进去了。我跟
to him what a [__] that's brilliant
他说：“卧槽，这太棒了！”
because usually I'm like I spend 10
通常我都会花10
seconds trying to figure out if they're
秒钟判断对方是不是想
trying to sell me something so I can
推销东西，然后赶紧继续忙自己的事。
just crack on with my day but for him to
但
be so honest with me by the way he
他竟然这么坦诚，直接跟我说：“顺便说一下，
literally this is a cold call I'm going
这是个推销电话，我要跟
to tell you about a product if you don't
你介绍一个产品，如果你
want to take the call feel free to hang
不想接，
up now and I was like this is amazing
现在就可以挂断。” 我当时就想，这太不可思议了。
what is it he told me I went on their
他告诉我：“是什么产品？” 我去他们的
website I looked it up I said we use a
网站查了一下，他说：“我们用的是
different tool called brandwatch so but
另一个叫Brandwatch的工具。”
I said like this has been so inspiring
我说：“
your honesty with me that it was so
你的坦诚真的太鼓舞人心了！” 这让我觉得很
disarming yeah and I think people are
坦诚，是的，而且我认为人们
smarter than we give them credit for so
比我们想象的要聪明。
call that I've ever received is that you
我接到的每一个陌生来电都是这样的：
know they call Mingo hi Steve is it
他们会打电话给Mingo，问“嗨，史蒂夫，是
Stephen Bartlett I go who is it I think
Stephen Bartlett吗？”我回答“是谁？”我想应该
it was the Stephen Butler I go who is it
是Stephen Butler，我又问“是谁？”我回答“是的”，然后
Stephen Bartlett I go yeah they go
他们会问“
so what are you doing with your data
你们
infrastructure things at the moment
目前在数据基础设施方面有什么进展？
because we've got an offering and it's
因为我们有一个产品。”
like and then I'm like [__] get out of
然后我就想“赶紧走吧”，
there but it's but the honesty was so
但这种坦诚真的让人
disarming and people are smarter than we
卸下防备。人们比我们想象的要聪明。
give them credit for so when you go
所以当你跟
around telling your friends or your
朋友、
loved ones whatever or your work
爱人或者
colleagues that you can they know yes
同事说起这件事时，他们可能知道，是的，
they know yeah but you don't want to
他们知道，但你不想
totally so something I want to think you
完全……我想我们之前
talked about we talked about
聊过
relationships though a topic we haven't
人际关系，虽然我们还没有完全
touched on completely it's funny I know
深入探讨过这个话题。有趣的是，我知道
you wrote a book in 2000 and I'm gonna
你在2000年写了一本书，我
say eight that's when it was published
猜是8，那是它出版的年份，是的，
yeah the earliest version was actually
最早的版本。 其实那是
like 2002 it was a eBook that was full
2002年左右，那是一本电子书，里面全是
of hot pink and a lot of exclamation
亮粉色，还有很多感叹号。
that tells me everything about how you
这让我完全明白你
feel about the book today yeah I a I
今天对这本书的感受。是的，我
still stand behind the book today but I
今天仍然支持这本书，但它也
was just it's also an explanation of how
解释了
things evolve yeah right
事物是如何演变的。是的，
what's your journey been like with
你的爱情之路是怎样的？
romantic love oh my goodness so
哦，我的天哪，嗯，和
um challenging like most people one of
大多数人一样，充满挑战。
my biggest challenges was actually I've
我最大的挑战之一是，我从小就
known from a very very young age that I
知道自己
basically never wanted to be married or
基本上不想结婚生子。这是一种
so that was just like it was this inner
内在的认知。
you know many young girls at least my
你知道，很多年轻女孩，至少我的
friends they would fantasize about like
朋友，她们会幻想自己的
my wedding day and you know there was
婚礼，有
lots of dolls and okay this is my baby
很多娃娃，比如“这是我的宝贝”之类的。
and all that stuff and I just never had
但我从来没有过
any of those desires or inklings and as
这些欲望或想法。
I became a teenager like why do you
到了青少年时期，
think do you know I don't know besides I
你觉得为什么呢？我不知道，但我
know it's my truth and I have never
知道这是我的真实想法，我从未
wavered on it could it be related to
动摇过。这会不会和
your parents relationship at all it
你的父母关系有关？很有可能。在遇到
could it very well could prior to Josh I
Josh之前，我
would meet folks and and and be in
会遇到一些人，
relationship and they'd be like okay so
谈恋爱…… 他们会说，好吧，那
we're gonna get married then we're gonna
我们结婚，然后生
have kids and I'm like are you actually
孩子，我就想，你们真的在
listening because that's not what this
听吗？因为这不是我
thing wants so that's that is not the
想要的，这不是
path I'm on so it was actually really
我要走的路。所以，这真的非常非常具
really challenging
有挑战性，
um until I until Josh and I got together
直到2003年我和Josh在一起，
back in 2003 and I felt like I had found
我感觉找到了
my soul mate how much have you thought
我的灵魂伴侣。你有没有想过
about how your early experiences have
你的早期经历是如何
like impacted your attachment style when
影响你的依恋模式的？当
I look at some of my friends and the
我观察我的一些朋友和
relationships they have they often seem
他们的关系时，他们似乎经常
to mirror the model they learn in their
反映出他们在家庭中学到的模式。是的，
household yeah so I've actually gone so
我实际上思考过一些
a couple things this has been an area of
事情，这
Fascination for me mostly because a I
对我来说是一个很迷人的领域，主要是因为我
just want to be a really good partner
只想成为一个好伴侣，
and a good human and especially with
一个好人，尤其是和
Josh like we've had so many ups and
Josh，我们经历了太多的
downs oh my God Stephen we've done so
起起落落，天哪，Stephen，我们做了
much therapy and and I'm gonna share
很多心理咨询。我想分享
something I don't know if you have
一些事情，我不知道你是否
interviewed these this couple yet or
采访过这对夫妇，或者
you're familiar with their work but
你是否了解他们的工作，但
these folks in my opinion they were the
在我看来，他们是
game changers and it does relate to kind
改变游戏规则的人，这确实与
of early childhood Impressions and how
早期经历有关。 童年印象以及
we were brought up and how that impacts
我们的成长经历，都会影响我们
how you interact in your adult
成年后的
relationships so um the most
人际关系。就建立健康的亲密关系而言，
work that I've ever done when it comes
我做过的最具变革意义的工作
to having a healthy relationship is from
是
Harvel Hendricks and Helen lekelly Hunt
哈维尔·亨德里克斯和海伦·莱凯利·亨特合著的《
so there's a book called getting the
获得
love you want it was like huge I think
你想要的爱》。这本书
in the 90s and then maybe the early
在90年代和
2000s I had never heard of it but Josh
2000年初非常畅销。我之前从未听说过，但
and I stumbled upon it when honestly we
我和乔什偶然发现了它。当时我们正处于非常
tough place and I didn't know if we were
艰难的时期，我不知道我们能否挺过去。
Josh had been talking with someone who
乔什当时和别人聊天，那人建议我们
was like oh you guys should try Imago
尝试意象
therapy which is the kind of therapy
疗法（Imago Therapy），这是一种由
that they have developed this whole body
他们发展起来的疗法，他们拥有一整套理论体系，而且都是
of work there's International therapists
国际知名的治疗师，
they're friggin fantastic I was like we
他们真的非常棒。我当时就想，我们一定要跟他们
must study with these people so they
学习。他们谈到，
kind of talk about the fact that every
每个
single person
人都会从
um you learn things in your family unit
家庭中学习一些东西。对
so for me there was a lot of kind of
我来说，
smothering that happened at certain
在某些
points so I need to be free I need to be
时候，我感到很窒息。所以我需要…… 自由，我需要
free and for Josh one of his kind of
自由。对乔什来说，他内心深处有一种创伤，
core and they use this language and you
他们用这种语言来描述，你
know it like a childhood wound for him
知道，就像童年创伤一样，对他而言是被
it was abandonment
遗弃，
so he wants to be close so oftentimes we
所以他渴望亲密。因此，我们常常
will pick the person that has the exact
会选择与自己
opposite childhood wound so for me
童年创伤截然相反的人。对我来说，
someone that wants freedom of course is
渴望自由的人当然会
going to choose a partner that wants
选择一个更渴望依恋的伴侣。
so
所以，
in their work it's actually like you
在他们的工作中，这实际上就像是
choose the perfect partner to heal the
选择完美的伴侣来治愈你自身
very things that you need to heal
需要治愈的创伤。
so for me that you are saying okay do
所以，你刚才说的“好吧，
you think that has to relate to just the
你认为这是否与
fact that I don't want to get married
我不想结婚有关？
just the fact that all that stuff does
所有这些事情
that really it probably does because
确实都与此有关”？很可能确实有关，因为
in my childhood a lot of me feeling very
我的童年时期，我非常渴望自由，却又感到非常
constricted and held back and so for
束缚和压抑。所以，对
Joshua was the opposite but I would
乔什来说，情况恰恰相反。
highly recommend their work if you have
如果你还没有了解过他们的工作，我强烈推荐你去尝试一下，
explored it it totally saved us well
它真的拯救了我们。
Josh you talk about the hard times in
乔什，你提到了2017年左右的艰难时期。我们经历了好几次……
had um so when my stepson was leaving
嗯，我继子要上
for college I think this was around
大学了，我想大概就是那时候吧。
maybe
大概是
2009 or 10. I might be getting the years
2009年或2010年吧。年份可能记错了，请见谅。总之，
wrong forgive me but um I was basically
我当时是个
workaholic and he was so just desirous
工作狂，他特别渴望得到我的
of just more attention and I was so
关注。我一心扑在
obsessed with my business and so
事业上，一心想
obsessed with trying to be successful
成功，害怕
and this fear if I slowed down that
一旦放慢脚步，这一切就会
would all be taken away then this fear
消失；又害怕
that if I didn't continue to work and
如果不再努力奋斗，不再努力
build that I was going to lose
发展，就会失去
everything and it almost destroyed my
一切。这种恐惧几乎毁了我们的
relationship it was terrible we had been
感情，真是太糟糕了。我们在一起
together about six or seven years we met
大概六七年了，
in 2003 so it's probably about 2010 and
2003年认识的，所以大概是2010年左右。
we had never once taken a proper
我们从来没有
vacation together
一起好好度假过，
because I always said that I couldn't
因为我总是说我太忙了，没时间。是
yeah
啊，
it's so funny
真有意思。
um I have a friend who is reminds me of
我有个朋友在
you so much in that way in the sense
这方面跟你很像，
that she has an immigrant story she came
她也是个移民，
to this country when she was super young
很小的时候就来到这个国家，在
in school she found some you know she
学校里被欺负，后来……你知道的……
she found they didn't have any money
她发现家里没钱，
that was the source of much of the pain
这是我们家很多痛苦的根源。
she started a business starts to go well
她开始创业，生意也开始走上正轨。
she doesn't want to get married she
她不想结婚，也
doesn't want to have kids her partner
不想生孩子。她的伴侣
has recently broken up with her because
最近和她分手了，因为她根本
her partner is not getting any time from
没时间陪伴伴侣，
her and she just works all the time
而她却一直在工作。
I watch her and I think you're being
我看着她，我觉得她是被
dragged by that fear of
那种害怕回到童年的恐惧所拖累，就像
being tied to the back of a car that's
被绑在一辆
just flying down the motorway yes and I
飞驰在高速公路上的车后一样。是的，我
just don't know what to say to her
不知道该对她说些什么，
because
因为
she
她
She's suffering the consequences of not
正在承受生活中缺乏
having connections or friends or love in
人际关系、朋友和爱情的后果。
her life yes but her ankle is attached
是的，但她的脚踝就像被绑在一辆
flying down the motorway her business is
飞驰在高速公路上的卡车后面一样。她的生意非常红火，
killing it when I say killing it I mean
我说红火，我的意思是
she's probably worth hundreds of
她可能身价
millions she's super young she's in a
数亿。她非常年轻，才二十出头，
um but she's unhappy but she can't get
但她不快乐，却无法
off the [__] Lorry it's dragging her
摆脱这辆该死的卡车，它拖着她。是的，
I think that it's really important for
我觉得，对
every person to come to that realization
每个人来说，意识到
they may be killing it in certain areas
自己在某些领域可能做得非常出色，
and then to be honest enough to say the
然后坦诚地指出哪些
areas where it's not working and then I
领域做得不够好，这一点非常重要。然后，我总是会
would always come back to if you want
回到“如果你想要什么”这个问题上来，就像
this it's kind of like we go back to
我们最终会发现，
everything is figure outable if having
一切皆有可能。如果你重视生活中的
love in your life friendships in your
爱、友谊、冒险和休闲
life Adventure in your life down time in
时光，那么
your life is important to you you can
你绝对可以找到解决办法。就
seen in my own journey and this is my
我个人的经历而言，
own personal estimation of myself I've
我
actually become way more successful I've
变得更加成功了。我
become a better Coach I've become a
成为了一个更好的教练、
better teacher I've become a better
更好的老师、更好的
friend I've become a better partner
朋友、更好的伴侣。我不再被
not being dragged by my drive
自己的动力所驱使，
not allowing
不再让
the fear of losing any success that I've
害怕失去已建立的成功
be the force that keeps me from the
成为阻碍我享受
richest parts of my life which are my
人生中最宝贵部分——人际关系——的力量。
connections for anyone who's who's in
对于任何正处于
that space right now they have to want
这种境地的人来说，他们必须渴望
to make that choice to change and then
做出改变的选择，并且
be willing to as much as they took the
愿意像当初
risk to start a business they have to be
创业那样
even more courageous to redefine their
勇敢地承担风险。 重新定义
own success at a higher different level
自己在更高层次上的成功，
and it takes courage takes a lot of
这需要勇气，非常大的
Courage so how did you redefine your own
勇气。那么，你是如何重新定义自己对
definition of success at a high level so
成功的更高层次的呢？
for me it was around really stepping
对我来说，这需要我真正地
back and asking myself what matters most
退后一步，问问自己什么才是最重要的，是
like is it the money in the bank account
银行账户里的钱，还是
is it the amount of followers or
粉丝或客户的数量，
customers or whatever and I remember
或者其他什么？我记得当时
sitting in that therapy chair and like
坐在治疗椅上，
thinking about what I've grown and then
思考着我成长了什么，然后
seeing this beautiful man and going like
看到这位英俊的男人，心想：
you know what it's not about choosing
你知道吗？这不是二选一的问题，
either or but like you've got a problem
而是你遇到了问题，
Marie and you got to fix this like this
玛丽，你必须解决这个问题。这
thing meaning the business cannot be
意味着，
your number one priority if you know in
如果你
your heart that love is the most
内心深处知道爱是
important thing in life then you need to
生命中最重要的事情，那么事业就不能成为你的首要任务，你需要
start demonstrating that you need to
开始展现出来，你需要
start acting that you need to start
开始行动，你需要开始
making time for that God you know in
为
your heart yeah so this is the
你的内心所爱腾出时间。是的，这很
interesting thing because we all know
有意思，因为我们都知道，客观上来说，
objectively no because we've read read
不，因为我们读过，读过，确实如此，我们相遇了，
that it's true we met you know I see
你知道，我经常看到这种情况，我们看到，我们
this a lot I see like we know we should
知道我们应该，这又回到了
goes back to kind of the wanting to want
想要拥有的
thing yeah I know that people are
东西。是的，我知道人们在……的
happier when they have friends and when
时候会更快乐。 他们有朋友，当
they have a romantic partner typically
他们有了伴侣时，通常会
relationship is formed I know that to be
形成某种动态关系。我知道这是
true
真的，
but I feel like I need to keep building
但我感觉我需要继续发展
this [__] business and climbing that
这个该死的生意，继续往上爬。
ladder and sure it's such an intense
当然，这是一种非常强烈、令人
strong all-consuming feeling just to
难以承受的感觉，就像要
keep on going keep throwing coal into
不断地往
the engine of this train yep but I know
这列火车的引擎里添煤一样。是的，但我知道我
I should spend time with my friends this
应该花时间陪朋友。这就是
is where I'm gonna go back well all this
我要回去的地方。所有这些
stuff so as it relates and I think those
事情都与此相关，我认为这
are maybe two different slight nuances
可能是两个略有不同的细微差别。
so I would go back to the Helen and the
所以我会回到海伦和
Harville work like there's a couple of
哈维尔的工作，
tools that they teach you one of which
他们教你一些工具，其中一个
is this tool called dialogue it's a very
叫做对话。这是一种
form of having a conversation with your
与爱人进行结构化对话的方式。
Stephen I cannot tell you how healing
斯蒂芬，我无法告诉你
this particular form of work is you
这种工作方式有多么治愈，你
could probably look it up online they do
可以在网上查一下。他们举办了
tons of workshops very inexpensively
很多工作坊，价格非常便宜。
they're actually even taking their
他们甚至把
workshops into police departments like
工作坊带到警察局，
because it is transformative how it
因为它具有变革性，它
helps people connect how it helps people
帮助人们建立联系，帮助人们
see each other how it helps people hear
彼此看见，帮助人们倾听
each other and how it helps people heal
彼此，帮助人们疗愈。
and when Josh and I started practicing
当我和乔什开始练习时，
these tools that we learned from from
从哈维尔和海伦那里学到的这些方法，让
something in me relaxed and I was able
我内心放松下来，能够
to see and hear and recognize and
看到、听到、识别并
understand Josh's needs in a way that
理解乔希的需求，而这种理解方式
did not feel threatening to my own drive
不会威胁到我追求成功的动力。就好像
previously those two things were at odds
以前这两件事是相互冲突的，但
and then all of a sudden everything was
突然之间，一切都
integrated where he felt really heard
融合了起来，他感到自己被真正倾听
and seen and I felt really heard and
和理解，我也感到自己被真正倾听和理解。
seen and it was as though that battle
仿佛那场斗争
completely disintegrated
彻底瓦解了，
and so no longer was it this or that no
不再是“要么
attention or you know what I mean I have
关注我，要么
to give up this business no it was like
放弃事业”这种二选一的问题。不，
oh now I understand what he really needs
现在我明白了，他真正需要的
which is not tons of time it's actually
不是大量的时间，而是
presence and giving him support and love
陪伴，是给予他支持和爱，让
in the way that he can really feel it
他能够真切地感受到。
and while he gets nurtured and it's
他需要被呵护，这和
completely different than how I do but
我以前的方式完全不同。但这
again this is like a practice and it's
就像一种练习，不是
nothing that we're taught in school so
我们在学校里学到的，所以
we're all just stumbling around at least
我们都在摸索前进，至少
I was and Josh and I were and now it
我和乔希都是如此。现在，
feels like Josh is so much more
乔希对我所做的一切都更加
supportive of all the things I do in my
支持了。
business and ironically not it's not
讽刺的是，我并不是不那么
that I care less but I'm less driven by
在意生意，而是不再那么害怕，而是
fear it's more driven by desire and fun
更多地被欲望、乐趣
and creativity and wouldn't it be cool
和创造力所驱动。
if oh let's try that and only saying yes
如果“哦，我们试试这个吧”，那岂不是很棒？我只对那些发自
to things that are like a full body yes
内心的事情说“
not saying yes to things because I think
是”，而不是因为觉得这样做能让
it's going to get me somewhere or it's
我有所成就，或者能让我的
going to you know get that bag so much
钱包鼓起来就答应。你知道吗，
bigger it's like you know what at some
有时候就是够了。
point enough's enough I'm sure you've
我相信你们也有过
experienced this it's like when does
这样的经历，就像在问：什么时候才算够？
quick word from one of our sponsors I've
来自我们赞助商的一条
got a tip for all of you that will make
消息：我有一个小技巧要分享给大家，它会让
your virtual meeting experiences I think
你们的虚拟会议体验提升
10 times better as some of you may know
十倍。你们中的一些人可能已经知道了，
by now Blue Jeans by Verizon offers
Verizon 的 Blue Jeans 提供
seamless high quality video conferencing
流畅的高质量视频会议。
but the reason why I use blue jeans
我之所以选择 Blue Jeans
versus other video conferencing tools is
而不是其他视频会议工具，是
because of immersion their tools make
因为它能带来沉浸感。他们的工具能让
you feel more connected to the employees
你感觉与
or customers you're trying to engage
你想要互动的员工或客户之间联系更紧密。
with and now they're launching one of
现在，他们推出了
impact virtual events so far called Blue
迄今为止影响虚拟活动的最大功能增强之一——Blue
Jean Studio I actually used it the other
Jean Studio。我实际上已经试用过了。 前
day I did a virtual event using the
几天我用 Blue Jean Studio 做了一场线上活动，大概有
studio which I think about 700 of you
700 位观众参与，
came to TV level production quality all
制作水平达到了电视级别，而且这一切都是由
done by one person with very little
一个
technical experience on a laptop so if
技术经验很少的人用笔记本电脑完成的。所以，如果
you've got an event coming up and you're
你即将举办活动，并且正在
thinking about doing it virtually check
考虑线上举办，那就赶紧去了解一下
out blue jean studio now let me know
Blue Jean Studio 吧！告诉我
what you think because I genuinely
你的想法，因为我真心
believe I know this is an advert and I'm
觉得它是目前为止
believe it's the best tool I've seen for
我见过的最好的工具，可以
doing really immersive simple but high
制作出沉浸感十足、简单易用但
quality production virtual events quick
质量极高的线上活动。另外，
one it's so crazy that in the last
最近
couple of months I've had so many people
几个月，好多人
tag me on Instagram even on Telegram and
在 Instagram、Telegram 甚至 Twitter 私信里标记我，分享他们
starting their heal journey and it's one
开始健康之旅的照片，这真是太不可思议了。能做播客是
of the most amazing things in my life
我人生中最棒的事情之一，
course needs money to to fuel and I have
当然，播客需要资金支持，而我的
a sponsor like you who I genuinely
赞助商就像你一样，我真心
believe is going to help every single
相信它能帮助每一个
person who starts their heel Journey
开始健康之旅的人
change their life because this podcast
改变人生，因为这个
the central intention of this podcast is
播客的核心宗旨就是
to help people live better lives and we
帮助人们过上更好的生活。我们
get to sit here and I get to promote to
坐在这里，我…… 我向
you a product which has not only helped
您推荐一款产品，它不仅
me change my life but it's going to help
改变了我的生活，而且正在帮助数百万人过上
millions of people live a nutritionally
营养
complete life it's so it's such an
均衡的生活，并且将会帮助数百万人。这是一款
incredible product and for me the reason
非常棒的产品。对我来说，它之所以如此
why it's incredible is because it gives
出色，是因为它能为我提供
me my protein it gives me my vitamins
蛋白质、维生素和
minerals it's plant-based it's low in
矿物质，而且它是植物基的，
sugar gluten free it does all of that in
低糖、无麸质的。所有这些营养成分都浓缩在
a small drink that tastes good there are
一杯美味的小饮料中。此外，还有
other products there's Foods there's the
其他产品，比如食品，还有
hot and savory collection many other
热饮。  d savory 系列还有很多其他
things but for me this ready to drink is
东西，但对我来说，这款即饮饮品
the absolute savior of my diet
绝对是我一周饮食的救星，因为
throughout the week where I'm moving at
我一周的工作节奏非常快。
such Pace look I don't want to labor the
我不想
point but if you haven't tried he'll
赘述，但如果你还没试过，一定要
give it a try and if you do tag me
试试。如果你试了，记得在
Instagram wherever you try it give me a
Instagram 或其他任何你尝试的地方标记我。
back to the podcast
回到播客，
I did actually want to ask because
我其实想问的是，因为
men don't often including me as a man we
男性（包括我作为男性）通常
don't often appreciate the social battle
不太能理解
women who say the things like I want to
女性在表达“我想
focus on my career yeah yeah I don't
专注于我的事业”、“我不想生
want to have kids I don't want to get
孩子”、“我不想
married sometimes undergo and I've I've
结婚”等想法时所面临的社会斗争、社会污名和批评。正
because I have these conversations now
因为如此，我现在经常和别人讨论这些问题，所以
I'm continually like cognizant of my own
我时刻意识到自己
bias in the way that I ask the questions
提问方式中的偏见。
yeah
那么，
how do you view all of that like how do
你如何看待这一切？
you view the the pressure that women
你如何看待女性
face to fall in line with the
面临的压力，她们被迫符合
old school stereotype of kids they're in
老派的“生孩子”刻板印象？她们身处一个
such a changing world yeah you know it's
瞬息万变的世界。你知道，这真的很
really interesting so one of the things
有意思。所以，在
I do on my show marietv is I answer
我的节目中，我会探讨这个问题。 在marietv，我
questions I love just taking questions
喜欢回答观众的问题。
one of our viewers said hey Marie how
一位观众问我：“嘿，Marie，
did you decide not to have kids and we
你为什么决定不要孩子？”我们
had never covered the topic before and I
之前从未讨论过这个话题。我就想，好吧，那我就来
talk about that and it was one of the
聊聊这个。结果这期节目成了
most popular episodes that we haven't
我们最受欢迎的节目之一，
we've ever had and it was because it
因为它
sparked this discussion just about
引发了关于
choice and about oh wow you just didn't
选择的讨论，以及“哇，你就是不想生孩子，
want them and you knew that it like
而且你知道这
wasn't a struggle and I'm like that's
并非什么难题”之类的讨论。我想，
maybe not everyone's journey and that's
也许这并非每个人的经历，这
great but I need to be honest about mine
很好，但我需要坦诚地谈谈我的经历。
because one of the things and we've had
因为我和
talks with my mom about this it's like
我妈妈也谈过这个问题，
her kind of set prescription was so
她从小就被灌输了一种观念：
you get married and you have kids and
结婚生子。
that was I think her authentic dream but
我想，这或许是她内心真正的梦想，但也是社会观念的束缚。
um I just think it's interesting I like
我觉得这个话题很有意思，我喜欢
talking about it because I think it's
谈论它，因为我认为
really important for every woman to know
每个女人都应该知道
that she has the right to choose her
自己有权选择自己的
Destiny and whether that Destiny
命运，无论是否要孩子。 命运
includes a family doesn't include a
包含家庭，但不包含
family includes some semblance of what
家庭，它包含某种程度上
she believes as a family like I want
她所认同的家庭模式。我希望
women to have that choice I can't tell
女性拥有这种选择权。我无法告诉
you how many comments were under that
你那条视频下有多少评论，很多
video people left comments anonymously
匿名人士留言，
who had given birth and absolutely loved
她们生了孩子，非常爱
their kids and said I would have made a
自己的孩子，并说
different choice if I knew I had one
如果早知道会这样，她们会做出不同的选择。
how many women feel that they must
很多女性觉得她们必须
follow this prescription and I think in
遵循这种既定的模式，这令人震惊。我想，在
2022 when we're recording this I'm like
2022年我们录制这段视频的时候，我简直惊呆了，心想：
I'm like no they don't have to and we
不，她们不必如此，我们
need everyone's gifts and it's like I
需要每个人的天赋。
just knew from the moment that I could
从我能
understand I was like that is not my
理解的那一刻起，我就知道，这不是我此生的
path in this lifetime my path in this
道路。我此
lifetime is to help people give birth to
生的道路是帮助人们孕育
their ideas and to possibilities it's
他们的想法和可能性，而
not necessarily to give birth to a
不是
physical child through my physical body
通过我的肉体生育一个孩子。
and so um I like to talk about it just
所以，我喜欢谈论这个话题，
because I want women to have as many
因为我希望女性拥有尽可能多的
choices as they possibly can to be as
选择，让她们能够
they possibly can
尽可能地展现才华、发挥影响力、获得幸福。当然，这
yeah certainly not setting off a topic
并不是在讨论一个
we talk about enough yeah because it
我们已经讨论过很多次的话题。 是的，因为这可以
goes back to these kind of like
追溯到这些相互
colliding narratives The Narrative is
冲突的叙事。这种叙事
much stronger that
非常强烈，比如，
you know you get married at the stage
你到了结婚的阶段，
you do this you get a mortgage you get a
你做了这件事，你买了房，
house you have your kids totally before
你生了孩子，
here if you don't you're a failure
如果你没做到这些，你就是个失败者。
that's right we all feel that men feel
没错，我们都感同身受。男人也会
it too in other ways but I think the the
以其他方式感受到这种压力，但我认为，
social pressure sometimes is a little
社会压力有时会
bit more intense on women to meet these
更强烈地作用在女性身上，迫使她们
deadlines in these timelines yeah
在这些时间节点上完成这些事情。是的，
time genius yes before we started
时间天才。是的，在我们开始
talking I asked you what was front of
谈话之前，我问过你
mind at the moment and you said time
此刻最关心的是什么，你说时间
genius yes why did you say that so uh
天才。是的，你为什么这么说？嗯，
probably for I would say almost a year
大概有一年半甚至
and a half if not two years so much of
两年的时间，我把
my own Creative Energy has been pouring
自己大量的创造力都投入
into this uh new program this new
到这个新项目，这个
experience that we created really born
我们创造的全新体验中，它实际上
out of my own pain I
源于我自身的痛苦。我在
hit a wall at the end of 2020 where I
2020年底遇到了瓶颈，我当时并
didn't realize how burned out I was I
没有意识到自己有多么疲惫。我想我们
think like many of us and I found myself
很多人都有这种感觉，我发现
myself in my whole career where I
自己陷入了职​​业生涯中从未经历过的境地，我
started dreading waking up in the
开始害怕早上醒来。
morning and so I went on this journey of
所以我开始了…… 这是一段
discovering and putting together like
探索和整合之旅，就像
how do we heal the Paradigm of living in
我们如何治愈
time stress and I described that where
时间压力下的生活方式一样。我描述过，
it's like you don't know what to focus
就像你早上醒来不知道该先做什么，
because there's so many things to do you
因为要做的事情太多了；
feel guilty if you take a rest for five
如果你休息五分钟，就会感到内疚，
minutes because your brain says I should
因为你的大脑会告诉你应该
be doing something more important you
做更重要的事情；你很难分清轻重缓急；
have trouble prioritizing you feel like
你感觉
no matter how many hours you put in It's
无论投入多少时间，都
never enough so we put together this
永远不够。所以我们开发了这个
program and it has honestly helped me so
项目，它真的帮了我
much and then I shared it with my
很多，然后我把它分享给了我的
audience I've never seen anything get
听众。我从未见过任何东西能给
results for people it has changed
人们带来如此大的效果，它彻底改变了我的生活。
everything for me I went on um what is
我接着问，这到底是什么？它
it it's there's there's really five key
实际上包含五个关键
parts to it first it's about changing
部分。首先，它从
our mindset from the inside out about
内而外地改变我们的思维模式，
getting out of time stress and living as
摆脱时间压力，成为
a Time genius where you know in your
时间管理大师，让你从内心
bones and in practice that there is
深处和实践中都明白，
always time for what's most important
总有时间去做最重要的事。
it's a complete different Paradigm again
这是一种完全不同的生活方式。
we can talk more about it it's a little
我们可以再详细讨论一下，
here the second part of it is when you
这里篇幅有限，无法面面俱到。第二部分是…… 当你
know it's important you can ignore
明白某件事重要时，你就可以忽略那些
what's not I found that for me in
不重要的事情。我在
different parts of my life and I'm
人生的不同阶段都体会到了
pretty good at this one but I can I'm
这一点，而且我在这方面做得相当不错。但我一直在
always practicing is if there's too much
练习的是，如果我肩负太多任务，
on my plate if everything's important
如果每件事都很重要，那就等于什么都不
nothing's important and then all of a
重要了。然后，
sudden I'm working all the time I've got
我就会突然发现自己一直在工作，同时处理着
17 plates in the air but when I have one
17件事。但如果我只有一个
project one primary project and
项目，一个主要项目，
everything else is kind of secondary my
其他一切都是次要的，我的
life has spaciousness I have Focus
生活就会变得轻松，我可以集中精力，
beautiful work gets done like it's just
工作也会出色地完成。这是
a different way to operate and you have
一种不同的工作方式，当你清楚地知道在人生的这个阶段什么才是最重要的，你就会更
such an easier time saying no to things
容易对一些事情说“不”。
then there's the third step is really
第三步是
about setting yourself up to win every
让自己
single day and we're all different in
每天都能成功。我们每个人在
this way so if you think about you know
这方面都不一样。想想看，你
do you like having a messy desk or a
喜欢凌乱的办公桌还是
clean desk
干净的办公桌？介于两者之间？
somewhere in the middle well I like
我喜欢
having a clean desk but my desk is
干净的办公桌，但我的办公桌
always messy but so you probably operate
总是很乱。所以你可能在这种状态下也能很好地工作，感觉很
comfortable for you I've survived thus
舒服，我目前为止都挺过来了。是啊是啊，
far yeah yeah yeah but some people are
但有些人
like I know people that are minimalist
就像…… 我认识一些极简主义者，
and you know it's like I love having my
你知道，就像我喜欢把
books around me I love having notebooks
书放在身边，把笔记本放在身边一样，
around me but a lot of people don't make
但很多人并没有构建
an ecosystem or design their environment
一个生态系统，或者说没有精心设计自己的环境
to really help them Thrive and then of
来真正帮助他们蓬勃发展。
course there's certain things we can do
当然，我们可以利用科技做一些事情
with technology to make sure we're never
来确保自己不会被
interrupted that distractions don't
打断，不会分心；
happen different things we can do with
我们也可以做一些不同的事情来锻炼
our brain
大脑。
um and then it's a lot about kind of
嗯，关键在于如何让
setting yourself up for follow-through
自己能够坚持下去，
and not relying on motivation which as
而不是依赖动力——
you know the silliest thing to rely on
你知道，动力是世界上最愚蠢的依赖。以上就是一个
brief overview of it but as I've been
简要概述。当我带领
walking people through this program and
人们体验这个项目，
seeing how fast they get results it just
看到他们如此迅速地取得成效时，
makes me happy because folks are they're
我感到非常高兴，因为他们的
lowering their stress levels they're
压力水平降低了，他们
having time to be with their kids
有时间陪伴孩子，
they're taking walks on the beach
在海滩散步，在更
they're getting more done in less time
短的时间内完成了更多的事情，
and they're not feeling exhausted
而且他们不再感到疲惫不堪。
anymore and so it's a really rewarding
所以这真的是一件很有意义的
thing one of the words I wrote down is
事情。我记下的一个词是“
multi-passionate yes yes
多才多艺”，是的，
you said you had ADHD yeah
你说你有注意力缺陷多动障碍（ADHD）。
is that somewhat linked to
这和
your multi-passionate entrepreneurialism
你的多才多艺的创业精神有某种联系吗？
it's it's a great question that I don't
这是一个很好的问题，但我不
know if I have a good answer to
知道我是否能给出完美的答案，
um because I'm certainly not a clinical
因为我当然不是临床
psychologist like I went to um the best
心理学家。我去看过
ADHD doctor in the country who gave me
全国最好的多动症医生，他给我做了
the diagnosis and he's like you have the
诊断，他说我很有
gift I'm like thank you I have the gift
天赋。我说谢谢，我确实有天赋，
thank you very much so I don't know if
非常感谢。所以我不知道
those two things are linked
这两件事之间是否有联系。
um but what I do know is anytime that
但我知道的是，每当
I've shared that phrase with many people
我跟很多人分享这句话时，
they're like oh my gosh I think I'm
他们都会说：“天哪，我觉得我也是
multi-passionate too it's the person
多才多艺的。” 这个人既有
that has this beautiful business and has
很棒的生意，又有
that art Instagram account and is an
艺术类的Instagram账号，而且还是一位
amazing Chef too and it just gives us
很棒的厨师。这
again it's a silly little phrase that
句话虽然听起来有点傻，但它就像一个
playground to talk about your different
游乐场，让你可以畅谈自己的不同
interests and maybe a way that doesn't
兴趣，也许还能
make you feel as broken as I did what is
让你不再像我以前那样感到沮丧。那么，
focus sit within that because that when
专注力又是什么呢？因为
people hear that they think of a lack of
人们一听到这个词，就会想到缺乏
focus yeah which is the as you say the
专注力。正如你所说，专注力恰恰是它的
antithesis of like entrepreneurial
反义词。 创业
advice it's like focus on something do
建议就像是专注于一件事，坚持
it for 10 is be consistent Focus so I
十年，保持专注。我
tried that that approach because I read
尝试了这种方法，因为我读了
about it so much and I'm like oh my gosh
很多相关的文章，心想天哪，
I must follow what everyone says because
我必须听从大家的建议，因为
that's the path to success and Stephen
那是通往成功的道路。斯蒂芬，
when I tried to just be a coach and just
当我尝试只做教练，同时兼职
do like the bartending on the side to
调酒
earn money I felt like I was cutting off
赚钱时，我感觉就像砍掉了自己的
a limb there were so many other pieces
一条胳膊。我内心还有很多其他的东西渴望
expressed and I was like what's wrong
表达，我心想，我到底怎么了？
with me why can't I just be a coach and
为什么我不能只做教练，
be happy and then do my bartending like
快乐地做调酒，
why can't it be that simple but I was
为什么就不能这么简单呢？当时我
probably um 23 or 24 and I love dance I
大概23、24岁，我热爱舞蹈，虽然我
was not a trained dancer it was just
不是专业的舞者，但舞蹈就像是
something that was in my body and in my
我身体和
soul and I sat down with myself and I
灵魂深处的一种东西。我坐下来认真思考，
did something called the 10-year test
做了一个叫做“十年测试”的事情。
this is something that has served me
这个测试也让我受益匪浅。
I thought I said okay Marie
我问自己：玛丽，
if when you're 34 and you look back and
如果你34岁的时候回首往事，发现自己
you did not at least try to make dance a
从未尝试过把舞蹈作为
part of your career will you regret it
你职业生涯的一部分，你会后悔吗？
and the answer was hell yes so when I
答案当然是肯定的。所以
was 24 even though I didn't have any
24岁那年，尽管我没有任何
dance training and it was just a passion
舞蹈训练，跳舞只是我的爱好，但
I started taking more dance classes and
我还是开始上更多的舞蹈课，也
I started teaching Fitness classes which
开始教健身课。这让
got me into a whole world of eventually
我进入了一个全新的世界，最终
becoming a Nike dance athlete but the
成为了耐克舞蹈运动员。但
point of that is I tried to follow that
重点是，我尝试过只走
path of one thing and I just failed
一条路，结果却惨败。
miserably and because I was so unhappy I
因为我太不快乐了，所以我
said all right [__] it I'm gonna pursue
说，好吧，去他妈的，我要追求
Dance I'm gonna pursue coaching I'm
舞蹈，我要追求教练，我
gonna do the bartending I'm going to let
要做调酒师，我要让
all of my different interests Thrive
我的所有兴趣爱好都蓬勃发展。我知道
knowing that I couldn't do that forever
我不可能永远只做一件事，我
I knew I wouldn't earn as much money as
知道我赚的钱不会像当教练那么多，
a coach I knew I was going to kind of
我知道我的
because my focus would be split but the
精力会分散，所以一切进展都会慢一些。但是，
giving myself permission to pursue all
允许自己追求所有
these different things far outweighed
这些不同的事情所带来的快乐和满足感，远远超过了
any slowness of growth or financial gain
成长速度或经济收益的缓慢。
I think that's the I think that's it I
我想，这就是
think um I was thinking about it as
我想说的。嗯，在
you're speaking and
你说话的时候，我一直在想这个问题。
the Trap there or the typically it will
陷阱，或者说通常情况下，
you know we get ourselves in really
我们会让自己陷入非常
complicated positions in life because
复杂的境地。 人生中的某些位置，因为像“
words a single word like find your
找到你的
passion it's a singular word yes so
激情”这样的词，虽然只有一个词，但它
missing on the end of it
结尾少了一个“s”，这
sends you a message that there should be
暗示着后面应该有
one it's an Easter egg and you need to
一个“s”，就像一个彩蛋，需要你
go and search for it you can you have to
去寻找。你必须
go and find it you know all these words
去找到它。你知道，所有这些词语有时会
can [__] us up sometimes in life and one
在生活中误导我们。我认为，
up when they're thinking about what you
当人们思考你
just said is
刚才说的话时，其中一个容易让人困惑的词是，
I think at the start of you said
你一开始说的“
something like I know I wouldn't be as
我知道我不会那么
successful yes because of the the
成功”，是的，因为
definition we're using for success in
我们对成功的定义
that case is not happiness you just
并非幸福。你
ended up saying like I was way more
最终说的是“我会更
fulfilled and way more but I wouldn't
充实，更快乐”，但我不会
make as much money so if you if I'm
赚那么多钱。所以，如果你一直以来对
of success had always been happiness
成功的定义都是幸福，
and if that was your guiding your North
如果幸福一直是你的指路
Star then of course you'd become a
明灯，那么你当然会成为一个
multi-passionate entrepreneur but if
充满激情的企业家。但如果
your definition of success which nobody
你对成功的定义——没人会这么
says it's just making shitloads of money
说——仅仅是赚很多钱，
and ignoring all the sort of branches of
而忽略了所有其他的
expression that we all have and all of
表达方式，那么…… 我们都拥有，而且
Interest we have then of course you
我们都对它们感兴趣。当然，如果你继续
would have probably focused on coaching
专注于教练工作，
you might have been a bigger coach as
你可能会成为更成功的教练，就像
you said like you might have been you
你说的，你可能会成为……你
know whatever not that you you didn't
知道的，等等。并不是说你最终没能
get there anyway but because you did but
达到那个高度，而是因为你做到了。
you know it might have been faster let's
你知道，也许会更快，这么说吧。
say yeah but I think it would and the my
但我认为会更快。我的
counter to that was this so all of that
反驳是这样的：所有这些
experience like teaching with Nike and
经历，比如在耐克教课，以及
targets and and Walmarts in the states
在美国的一些奇怪的Target和沃尔玛等商店拍摄视频，甚至还有我以前
like there's actual DVDs of me on
在
Fitness videos back when there was like
健身视频里拍的DVD，
this and like you know what I mean
你知道我的意思。
because but all of that experience set
所有这些经历都让
me up to start my own YouTube show set
我能够创办自己的YouTube节目，
me and it brought all of these different
并将所有这些不同的
expressions and
表达方式和
influences into my brand that lived
影响融入到我今天的品牌中，这使它与
than other people you know there's some
其他人非常不同。你知道，有些
people that are coaches that are
教练很
brilliant and they have this beautiful
优秀，他们拥有优秀的
academic background or different things
学术背景或其他方面的优势，而对
and for me all of that flavor made its
我来说，所有这些特质都融入
way in and it gave me the confidence and
其中，给了我自信，
and I think a uniqueness that um
我认为也赋予了我独特的个性，使
actually made the business that I have
我
today so much more rich and so much more
今天的事业更加丰富，更加独特。
unique unique and um and joyful to run
奔跑的乐趣，
that's exactly what creativity is isn't
这正是创造力的本质，不是吗？
it it's having
它意味着拥有
rare and uh unique points of inspiration
罕见而独特的灵感
and experience and bringing them
和经验，并将它们融合
together to create something new so like
在一起，创造出新的事物。比如，
you know you're doing Fitness stuff yes
你知道，你在做健身相关的工作，
one can see how the lessons you learned
人们可以看到你在那里学到的东西
are still in the work you do today and
仍然在你今天的工作中发挥作用。
the example as I look down at this iPad
就像我低头看着
in front of me that I that I always talk
面前的iPad一样，我总是会提到它，它说明了看似
straight seemingly strange things can
奇怪的事物
end up defining you seemingly strange
最终如何定义你。看似奇怪的
creative Inspirations can Define you as
创意灵感可以定义你，就像
is the iPad and apple and knowing that
iPad和苹果公司一样。要知道，
Steve Jobs taking that typography class
史蒂夫·乔布斯参加的那门字体设计课程
was ultimately the reason much of the
最终成为了
reason why apple is they care so much
苹果公司成功的重要原因之一。苹果公司非常注重
about design and Detail in typography
设计和字体设计的细节，
and that set them apart from other
这使他们与其他
brands which I won't name and you'd
品牌区别开来（我就不点名了，你可能
never think that would make sense and
觉得这很矛盾）。
but he cites that in his commencement
他在毕业
speech he cites these really obscure
演讲中提到了这些他参加的非常冷门的
classes he took as being the reason why
课程，并称正是这些课程造就了
apple is what it is today but in typical
今天的苹果公司。但是，在典型的
narrative we say to like if you want to
叙事中，我们会说，如果你想
be a coach go do a course on how to be a
成为一名教练，那就去参加一个如何成为
coach just that like right don't [__]
教练的课程，仅此而已，对吧？ 去他妈的
music right which could be a great [__]
音乐，对吧？去他妈的
breath work or this meditation class you
呼吸练习或者你想上的冥想课，去他妈的
want to do [__] all these other things
其他所有东西，
Focus yeah but the best those that
集中注意力，没错。但最好的，那些
create really unique feeling stuff that
创造出真正独特、
the world really has never seen or felt
世界前所未见、
before but needs are those that
前所未闻，但却是人们真正需要的东西的人，是那些
pulling Inspirations from the most
从最
bizarre Unthinkable places to create a
离奇、最不可思议的地方汲取灵感来创建
new coaching business that's right what
新教练事业的人。
now it's less of a struggle more of uh
没错，你现在在挣扎什么？与其说是挣扎，不如说是……嗯，
this is what I'm playing with and I'm
这就是我正在尝试的，
I'm I'm excited about getting better at
我很兴奋能做得更好。
you know I'm here to give a beautiful
你知道，我来这里是为了
talk in an event and it's something that
在一个活动上发表一场精彩的演讲，这是
I haven't done a lot of because we've
我以前很少做的事情，因为我们
been in covid and all this stuff and I
经历了新冠疫情等等。我会在
can get nervous on stage I can get
台上紧张，真的会很
really nervous like I'm very very
紧张。我非常非常
comfortable with cameras and having
适应镜头和
one-on-one conversations but I can get
一对一的谈话，但当
super nervous on stage when it's not
台上不是
like my people that have come to see me
我的粉丝来看我的时候，我会超级紧张。
so that's something that I've been
所以这是我
working on a lot this year what does
今年一直在努力克服的事情。
that mean in a like a detailed a
从具体、实际的角度来看，这意味着什么？
that's the thing you're struggling with
你正在努力克服的问题是
is it so it's an anxiety a fear yeah
焦虑还是恐惧？是的，
sometimes it's it's about oh my gosh you
有时候是这样。天哪，你
know people will ask me to come speak on
知道，人们会邀请我上台演讲，在
stage different stages and and I've said
不同的舞台上，但我经常拒绝，
no so often because I have so many other
因为我有很多其他
things that my attention's on and I'm a
事情要忙。
person I I like to prepare and I like to
我喜欢做准备，喜欢
deliver as much value as I can I want to
尽可能地展现价值，我想照顾好
take care of a host and Their audience
主持人和听众。
and like putting together I'm like oh
就像准备
gosh what's the talk gonna be like I can
演讲稿一样，我会想，天哪，演讲会是什么样子？我
feel my mind going into a super swirly
感觉我的思绪开始混乱，
place and it's not fun and it was like I
这很不好受。我当时想，我
need to handle this I'm like I don't
必须解决这个问题。但我又不想
need to handle this on my own you know
独自面对，你知道，
everything is figureoutable but that
所有问题都可以解决，但这
doesn't mean that I can't ask for help
并不意味着我不能寻求帮助。
figuring it out so for me it's it's
所以对我来说，关键在于克服
um working through the anxiety and the
焦虑和
nerves around okay well how can I
紧张，比如，我该如何
construct the best talk how long should
构建一个最好的演讲？演讲应该持续多久？如何
it be the delivery how many stories like
表达？要讲多少个故事？等等，
a lot of kind of technical things it's
很多技术性的问题。这听起来可能很复杂。
it might sound really silly I don't know
傻乎乎的，我不知道是不是这样，
if it does or not but it's things that
但我
like my head just goes like this about
脑子里总是冒出一些想法，
and I'm like okay where does that come
然后我就想，好吧，这些想法是
from in you I don't know I think that um
从哪里来的？我不知道。我觉得，嗯，
one of the things I've seen about myself
我发现自己的一个特点
is that when I do something enough times
是，当我做某件事足够多次时，
I get super comfortable with it and then
我会变得非常得心应手，然后
I can be really creative and playful
我就能变得很有创造力，很会玩。
and so I think it's honestly a lack of
所以我觉得，说实话，是因为
having done it a lot recently like when
最近我做得太少了。比如
I was on book tour it was just like ah
我上次的签书会，感觉就像，啊，真的
like it was so much fun and it had like
很有趣，而且
a very clear Focus I was like oh we're
目标非常明确，我会想，哦，我们在
talking about the book and all the
谈论这本书，所有
content was right there but when things
内容都在那里。但是当事情
are more free form I'm so creative that
更自由的时候，我的创造力就会变得非常
it can get like wild and crazy so I want
旺盛，甚至有点疯狂。所以我想要给
to put containers around stuff and give
事情设个框架，给
myself more opportunities to do it in a
自己更多机会，以一种
way where it feels really fun
真正有趣的方式去做。那么，就
what about personally what are you
个人而言，你有什么
struggling with personally that was a
困难吗？刚才那只是个
professional example okay personally
职业方面的例子。好吧，就个人而言，我
I don't and this is not I'm probably
没有困难。我知道这么说可能
gonna sound like a total [__] so I'll
听起来像个混蛋，但我还是直
just say that out loud at this
说了吧，我现在真的
particular moment I don't feel a sense
没有。
consistently in my personal life like I
在我的个人生活中，我一直感觉在某件事上挣扎。我
feel I spent so much time over the past
觉得过去几年我花了很多时间——
couple of years we're talking about the
我们说的是
time genius stuff like really taking
时间管理方面——真正地
care of my mental health and really
照顾我的心理健康，
starting to kind of unprogram and
开始摆脱和
reprogram some of the stuff that I've
重新调整一些我
tortured myself with in the past that I
过去一直折磨自己的想法，
finally feel such a level of peace and
最终我感到了一种平静和
acceptance of like who I am and Josh and
接纳，我和乔什一起
I have done so much work and I feel so
做了很多努力，我非常
grateful and he's the person I spend the
感激。他是我相处
most time with
时间最长的人，
and we have just such a I'm so grateful
我们之间有着非常深厚的感情，我非常感激
for our relationship so in the personal
我们的关系。所以，就个人
realm there's not one that comes up
层面而言，现在没有什么特别突出的问题，但这
right now that doesn't mean it's not
并不意味着以后不会
gonna come up with Josh yes if I'd
和乔什谈到这个问题。如果我
called him this morning and I said Josh
今天早上打电话给他，问他“乔什，
what does Marie struggle with personally
玛丽在个人方面有什么困扰？”，
yeah what would he say he might oh I
他会怎么说呢？哦，我
know what he would say he would probably
知道他会说什么，他可能会
say
说，
um being hard on herself
嗯，她对
being hard on herself like I like
自己太苛刻了。就像
basically before I was coming here and
我来这里之前，
getting I was like you think the Talk's
我问他“你觉得这次谈话会顺利吗？”，
gonna go okay he's like it's gonna go
他说“会很顺利的”，
great like you know I can have those
你知道，我可以…… 那些
like just like is it gonna all be okay
就像“一切都会好起来吗？”之
like that kind of stuff and um
类的问题，
yeah I think he's just like you he's
嗯，我觉得他就像你一样，他一直鼓励我
consistently my Champion for being nicer
善待
to myself like if he catches me
自己。有时候他能察觉到，我
sometimes I won't catch it myself if I'm
自己可能都没意识到，比如我
going into a mode of like really getting
进入了一种非常
focused and you know maybe working a
专注的状态，工作时间
little too long is like have you eaten
有点长了，他就会问“你吃饭了吗？”，我会说“
I'm like thank you because I have not or
谢谢”，因为我还没吃呢，或者
something like that are you still being
诸如此类的问题。“你还在被
dragged
拖着走吗？”
you know I don't feel that way
你知道，我并不觉得那样，这
that that's the honest to goodness truth
是实话。
we had a there was a couple of
我们之前有过几次
opportunities that came up specifically
机会，尤其是在
around this trip and I heard that you
这次旅行前后，我听到有人说你
should do that right I heard that voice
应该去，对吧？我听到了那个声音，
I was and I just politely declined and I
但我礼貌地拒绝了，我一点
didn't feel any guilt about it I was
也不觉得内疚。说实话，这对
like it that felt new for me to be
我来说感觉很新鲜，
honest because I've gone on trips and
因为我以前也出差旅行过，
every moment of every day you know what
每天的每一刻都安排得满满当当，你知道
I mean was packed so that you could
我的意思吗？这样才能抓住
maximize every opportunity and before I
每一个机会。在我
came here to see you like I was with my
来见你之前，我和我的
team and like shopping for a pair of
团队在一起，当时我正在逛街，想买一条
jeans that I really wanted
我特别想要的牛仔裤。
chapter 10. yes
第十章里一切都能得到解决，这真是太好了。是的，
the world needs your special gift yes
世界需要你的特殊天赋，没错，这
that's what that's the name of the
就是这一章的标题。
um there's a quote you say most high
嗯，你说过一句名言：大多数
Achievers struggle with feeling like a
成功人士都挣扎于觉得自己像个
fake but never talk about it
骗子，但他们从不谈论这种感觉，
it's like a dirty little secret
这就像一个每个人都害怕的肮脏小秘密。
everyone's afraid to admit I'll tell you
说实话，
I still feel this way at times and I've
我有时还是会有这种感觉，我已经
been doing this work for almost two
从事这项工作快二
decades
十年了。
do you feel like a fake sometimes oh
你有时觉得自己像个骗子吗？哦，是的，我的
yeah I mean what we were just talking
意思是，就像我们刚才聊的，关于
about with um the speaking thing like I
演讲这件事，我
have the voice in my head Stephen like
脑子里有个声音。斯蒂芬，
you've been coaching and working with
你从事教练和与
people for over 20 years like why are
人合作超过20年了，为什么
you how do you still have anxiety about
你还会对
getting up on a stage I can see emotion
上台感到焦虑？我能看出
in your face oh totally because it's
你脸上的情绪。哦，完全是这样，因为感觉就像有
like so much
很多
judgment like it's still there even
评判，
though I do it it's but it's like I
即使我努力做到，它仍然存在。我
the time and she was like Marie you're
经常和我的好朋友谈论这件事，她说：“玛丽，你
doing great but I was like I still have
做得很好。”但我说：“我仍然有
that voice that's like you should be
那个声音，它说你应该
able to just walk up on any stage at a
可以随时随地走上任何舞台，
moment's notice and like [__] crush
然后大放异彩。”
it but it's just not the truth I can't
但这并非事实，我做不到。
do that and so that voice is still there
所以那个声音仍然存在，
and when I hear it I continue to
当我听到它时，我会继续
practice to be kind to myself and go
练习善待自己，告诉自己：“
it's okay you're doing okay
没关系，你做得很好。”
do you feel like you're enough
你觉得自己足够好吗？
I and I'm better at this than I've ever
我比以前更擅长做这件事了，
been I'm not nowhere near perfect please
我离完美还差得远，拜托别这么说，
no but I am so much less susceptible
但我现在比以前不容易受影响了。
you know like I was telling you about
你知道吗，就像我跟你说过，有人说
that person that said you're so good at
你这么擅长
what you do like why aren't your numbers
你做的事情，为什么你的粉丝数量不多？
bigger that conversation
那次对话让
I felt like such [__] right and it was
我感觉糟透了，对吧？我当时就想，
just like oh God you know like you have
天哪，你知道，
you've been doing it why aren't your
你一直在做这件事，为什么你的粉丝
numbers bigger like so that if I'm in if
数量不多？所以，如果
I get sucked into that conversation I
我被卷入那种对话，我
absolutely do not feel like enough a
绝对会觉得自己不够好。
hundred percent when I have enough
当我拥有足够的
perspective or when I can you know what
视角，或者当我能够……你知道我的意思，比如
I mean like get sober from that I'm like
摆脱那种影响的时候，我就会想，
dude everything is like I'm so happy how
老兄，一切都那么美好，我该如何摆脱它呢？
do I get sober from that
我摆脱它的
one of the ways that I did I realized
方法之一是，我意识到，
that uh for me and this was just me
对我
personally
个人而言，沉迷
being on social was not healthy for me
社交媒体并不健康。
it was not because you know in any given
因为你知道，在任何
moment you're either like engaged in
时刻，你要么全身心投入到
your life and creating and like just
你的生活中，要么在创造，要么在
being with people you're making a meal
和别人在一起，要么在做饭，
or you know like whatever you do or for
或者你知道，无论你在做什么，对
me like even just being on there it's
我来说，即使只是待在社交媒体上，也是不健康的。
like it's almost like a little thought
就像一条小
worm gets in and then at two o'clock in
虫子钻进我的脑袋，然后凌晨两点
the morning you wake up and you're like
你醒来，开始想：
why am I not doing x and x like so and
为什么我没有像某某那样做这做那？
so is or I should be doing this like
或者我应该做这个？就是那种“
it's that whole conversation I should be
我应该
wanting this or I should be doing this
想要这个”或者“我应该做那个”的对话。
and I found it to be really toxic for me
我发现这对我来说真的很有害，很不
I found it to be really unhealthy for me
健康。我会想：
where I was like wow if I'm on this
哇，如果我用这个，我就会忍不住跟别人
thing I find that I'm comparing myself
比较；而
and when I'm not on this thing I'm like
不用的时候，我又会觉得：是
yeah like I'm so happy I'm CR like I'm
啊，我好开心，我感觉自己很有
really creatively productive I'm more
创造力，我的作品更多了，
prolific like I'm a better leader I'm a
我是个更好的领导者，我是个
better partner I'm just happy so I
更好的伴侣，我就是很开心。所以我几乎不用社交媒体，我根本
don't do it at all there'll be people
不用。
you know that want to be coaches or that
我知道有些人想当教练什么的，
yeah because you careers in creating
因为他们的事业是创造，是的，他们也有
that yes that feel the same way yeah but
同样的感觉。但是
they could buy my business yeah how do I
他们可能会收购我的公司，
business if I'm not on social media sure
如果我不用社交媒体，我的事业怎么成功？ 当然，
sure I think that there are really
我认为有很多非常
helpful and useful ways to do so and I
有用的方法可以做到这一点，而且我
think that it doesn't have to take a lot
认为这并不需要花很多
of money it just takes a little bit of
钱，只需要一点
creativity and it takes some really
创意，以及一些非常
strong personal boundaries and standards
坚定的个人界限和标准。
so for instance at this point in the
例如，在目前这个阶段，
you know I have a team you've met some
你知道，我有一个团队，你今天也见过其中的一些成员，
of them today like we'll create content
我们会创作内容，然后由他们
and they'll post it it's not much
发布。这和
different than me with my YouTube show
我做YouTube节目
or my podcast I'm not necessarily the
或播客没什么区别，我不一定亲自
one going on YouTube to upload things
去YouTube上传内容，你明白我的意思吗？
dude oh I have no money well this is
哦，我没钱。嗯，这
something you could probably get an
你可以雇个
intern this is one of the things that's
实习生。这是所有事情都可以解决的其中一点，
everything is figure outable you can
你
absolutely figure it out like even if
绝对可以找到解决办法。即使
you had to work a little bit extra if
你需要额外工作，比如像
you were a bartender like me or waiting
我一样做调酒师或
tables and one of your shifts was
服务员，你用一个班次来
devoted to hiring someone to post things
雇人帮你发布内容，
for you you could figure it out or you
你也能找到办法，或者你
could set limits for yourself you know
可以给自己设定一些限制。你知道
Instagram and I don't know because I
Instagram，我不太
don't know much about the app because
了解这个应用，因为
I'm not in there much but um I know that
我不怎么用它，但我知道
you can turn off or at least mine is you
你可以关闭，或者至少…… 我的想法是，你
don't have to see the amounts of likes
不必去看
on anything you just actually see an
任何东西的点赞数，你只需要看到
image or whatever and so you can kind of
图片或其他内容。这样你就可以
craft the tools so that you keep
打造一些工具，让
yourself away from the things that [__]
自己远离那些会让
you up yeah and then you go on and I
你崩溃的东西。然后，我把
showed this to an artist friend of mine
这个方法分享给了我的一位艺术家朋友，
who is absolutely drowning because she
她现在非常焦虑，因为她
was comparing herself to all these other
一直在和别的
artists and I showed her how to mute
艺术家比较。我教她如何屏蔽一些比较
things because she loves those human
信息，因为她很喜欢那些
beings but it's just her own ego gets so
艺术家，但她的自尊心太强了。她真心
such right so it's like she wishes all
希望所有人都能成功，
of these people well she's a beautiful
她是一个很棒的
person who wants everybody to be
人，希望每个人都能
successful but like most of us it's
成功，但就像我们大多数人一样，比较是
built into our neurology it's built into
根植于我们的神经系统和
our biology to compare ourselves and if
生物学中的。如果
you spend enough time on that you're
你在这方面花费太多时间，最终只会
gonna wind up feeling like [__] it's
感觉很糟糕。很
funny you said something earlier where
有意思的是，你之前说过，
we were talking about kids and you said
我们聊到孩子的时候，你说
the advice you'd like to give to women
你想给女性的建议
is just all the The Narrative you'd like
是，你想
to put out there to women is that by the
传达给女性的信息是，使用
that to me about social media that like
社交媒体是一种选择。是的，从来没有人跟我说过，
I could be intentional yes about how I
我可以有意识地使用它。 我是怎么
use it we download the app it says put
用的？我们下载这个应用，它说要输入
your name in we do as we're told and
你的名字，我们就照做。
then it quite clearly because of the
然后很明显，因为
comparison psychology we're like okay I
攀比心理，我们会想，好吧，我
need to make this number bigger and
需要让这个数字更大，让
these numbers as big as possible that's
这些数字尽可能大。这就是
what I'm doing here
我现在正在做的。
the pause I had maybe a couple of years
我大概两年前停下来想，
the harm is done in I'm choosing to
伤害已经造成了。我选择
follow people and this like a library is
关注别人，而这就像一个资料库，
now the greatest influence over my world
现在成了我世界观的最大影响来源。
view my view of myself in the world is
我对自身在世界上的看法，就是
the me just hitting that follow button
我点击关注按钮。
I'll follow Kim Kardashian Kylie oh this
我会关注金·卡戴珊、凯莉·詹娜，哦，这个
account's called get rich become a
账号叫“致富，成为
millionaire and it's posting
百万富翁”，它发布
Lamborghinis follow and what you're
兰博基尼的照片，关注它。你这样做，就是
with junk values and then you're going
用垃圾信息填充你的资料库，然后你会为此
to pay the price you're going to pay the
付出
price for that so this idea that I could
代价。我大概三年前想到可以把
just mute everyone
所有人都屏蔽掉。说
honestly if you're listening to this and
实话，如果你正在听这段话，而
I follow you there's a reason why I'm
我关注了你，那我
not in your story views because 95
没出现在你的故事浏览量里是有原因的，因为95
percent of people are muted
%的人都被屏蔽了，
the people that really matter have my
真正重要的人都屏蔽了。 我的
WhatsApp they send me like inappropriate
WhatsApp上有人给我发一些不合适的
gifts and completely memes and stuff
礼物和表情包之类的东西，
like you know where I'm at yep so yeah
你知道我在哪儿，对，所以，
and I'd never post anything personal in
我从来不在上面发布任何
terms of what I'm doing in my life where
关于我生活、
I go on holiday what I drive whatever on
度假、开车之类的个人信息。
there anyway I don't want to play those
反正我不想玩那种
games I post ideas yeah and um I
游戏，我只会发布一些想法。嗯，
actually don't post myself either
其实我也不发自己的照片，
because I'm fortunate enough to have a
因为我很幸运地有一个
team but yeah that that point about
团队。但是，
and that is you know that's really the
你说的重点是要认真选择工具，这才是
key point because all the rest of it and
关键，因为其他的一切都无关紧要。并不是说
haven't I have posted and if I was
我没发过东西，我发过，如果让我
starting over again and I felt like that
重新开始，我会觉得这
was actually a good tool for my message
确实是个很好的工具，可以传递我的信息，然后
to get out and I said okay this is great
我会想，好吧，这对
for me how can I batch yeah how can I do
我来说很棒，我该如何批量发布？我该怎么做
this and get great I'm going to schedule
才能做得更好？我要安排一下发布时间。有很多
kinds of different tools and to your
不同的工具。说到你刚才说的，
point I loved the word that you used how
我很喜欢你用的那个词：
can I be intentional about this how can
我该如何有意识地使用这个工具？我该如何以一种能够
to help me serve and connect with people
帮助我服务和连接的方式使用这个媒介？ 和那些
that I really want to connect with and
我真正想建立联系的人在一起，
absolutely minimize or eliminate the
尽可能地减少或消除
downsides and you can and you can and I
负面影响，你可以做到，而且你可以做到，我
think that's what's really really
认为这才是真正
important and I think there's too many
重要的。我觉得太多
people who think that you have to be on
人认为你必须
it all the time and for some people if
时刻在线，有些人如果
they enjoy it I'll meet like go on with
乐在其中，我会说“继续做
your bad self I just realized that's not
你自己吧”，但我意识到我不是那样的人。
me we don't realize the role that media
我们没有意识到媒体
is having on our values and our psyche
对我们的价值观、心理、
and our mental health and our well-being
心理健康和幸福感的影响。
um I read this wonderful study he
我读过一项很棒的研究，他让
basically exposed them to certain media
孩子们接触某些媒体，比如一个带有
toy in it versus the children that
玩具的广告。然后，研究人员将看过广告的孩子和
didn't watch the advert with a toy in it
没看过广告的孩子进行比较，
were then asked who do you want to play
问他们想和谁玩：一个
person that's holding the toy or a
拿着玩具的非常讨厌、非常刻薄的人，还是一个
lovely kid that didn't have the toy
没有玩具的非常可爱的孩子。结果，
that had seen the advert always chose to
看过广告的孩子总是选择和那个拿着玩具的
the nasty kid with the toy and what that
讨厌孩子一起玩。 玩具，以及由此可见，
shows is how the media that influence
媒体对
the glamorization of that toy shifted
玩具的过度美化是如何从根本上改变
your values at a really fundamental
你的价值观的。
level and if you think about that you
想想看，如果你把目光
zoom out on an adult's life and how
放宽到成年人的生活，就会发现
something they see consume in this
他们在数字图书馆里看到和消费的东西，
Digital Library can make them skew their
会如何扭曲他们的
orientation towards junk values and how
价值观，让他们走向消极的人生，最终导致空虚、
unfulfillment a burnout ad connections
倦怠、
bad relationships you've got to be
人际关系破裂。所以，你必须
intentional yes about that Library I'll
有意识地去使用数字图书馆。是的，关于这个图书馆，我还要
say one thing too that I've shared with
说一点，我之前也跟
my audience that maybe some folks in
我的观众分享过，也许你们中的一些人
yours will find useful especially if you
也会觉得有用，特别是如果
or other media content when you first
你早上醒来第一件事就是浏览社交媒体或其他媒体内容的话。
wake up in the morning I think 85
我认为85
percent of folks who own cell phones do
%的手机用户都会在
create before you consume
消费之前先进行创造。
create before you consume whether it's
无论是
creating a stronger mindset a stronger
培养更强大的心态、更强壮的
body spending time in nature being with
身体、亲近自然、陪伴
your partner writing that song creating
伴侣、创作歌曲、创作
that piece of art just create before you
艺术作品，总之，在消费之前先进行创造。
consume and it's like a really fun
这就像一个很有趣的
Mantra that you can use anytime during
口号，你可以在一天中的任何时候使用。
the day like if you're going to pick up
比如，当你
your phone because you're insecure
因为缺乏安全感、
you're uncertain you're uncomfortable
不确定或感到不舒服而想要拿起手机时，就提醒自己：
you're fearful you don't know what to do
害怕不知道
next so you're like well let me go for
下一步该做什么，所以你会想，好吧，让我先满足一下
my little you know addict thing create
我的小瘾吧。在
before you consume let it be a pause and
消费之前先创造，让它成为一个停顿，
ask yourself what do I really want to
问问自己，我现在真正想
create right now do I want to consume
创造什么？我想消费
other people's ideas do I want to get
别人的想法吗？我想
sucked into this hole or is there
陷入这个无底洞吗？还是我想
something I want to create is there a
创造点什么？
meal I want to make is there a walk I
我想做一顿饭吗？我想去散散步吗？我想
reach out to do I want to take a picture
联系哪个朋友吗？我想拍张照片
and send it to my best friend and say oh
发给我最好的朋友，说“
my God I'm thinking of you you know
天哪，我在想你”吗？你知道，
whatever it is but this notion of just
不管是什么，但这种在
creating before we consume again that's
消费之前先创造的想法再次
just been another one that's helped me
帮助了我，
it's so powerful it's so simple
它如此强大，如此简单，
and I definitely need to heed that
我绝对需要听从这个
advice because I wake up and I look at
建议，因为我醒来后看着眼前
my what's happening and say oh [__]
发生的一切，会说“哦，糟了”，
especially when you've got like Global
尤其是当你拥有像全球性
like businesses in different time zones
企业那样，业务遍及不同时区的时候。当然，
sure waking up to a crisis every day is
每天醒来都面对危机肯定
not the best place but listen Marie um
不是好事，但是听着，玛丽，嗯，
we have a closing tradition on this
我们这个
podcast where the previous guest asks a
播客有个结束的传统，上一位嘉宾会提出一个
question in the Diary of a CEO which is
问题……
on the table here this is the official
桌上这本《CEO日记》是官方的，
Diary of a CEO this is the one of one
是那种
um where they ask a question for the
会给下一位
next guest they don't know who they're
嘉宾提一个问题，但事先并不知道是谁
asking it for and I don't get to see it
提的，我得
until I open the book
翻开书才能看到。好了，开始吧。
so here we go handwriting is interesting
字迹很有意思。稍等片刻，你从
what lesson have you learned from your
人生
lowest point
低谷中学到了什么？
and is there anything about it that
有没有什么让
you're grateful for
你心存感激的？
um
嗯，
I don't know if there's one specific
我不知道有没有哪个特定的
lowest point but I'll just I'll I'll
低谷，但我
choose one
选一个吧。
that I learned from a low point
我从低谷中学到的教训
was to
是
always trust my instincts and to not
永远要相信自己的直觉，
wisdom to not Outsource what I should do
不要把智慧外包出去，不要把该做什么外包出去，不要指望
to not look to other people
别人来告诉我，因为我内心深处就蕴藏着
to find the wisdom that already is
智慧。
within me and I think that trusting of
我认为，信任内心的
that little voice and to never ever ever
声音，永远永远永远永远不要
ever doubt it
怀疑它，这
that was probably
大概就是
um that's the lesson I I keep getting in
我人生中不断领悟并不断实践的教训，
my life and I I keep adhering to and
而且我还在
learning on different levels and am I
不同的层面上学习它。我对此心存
grateful for it 100 because I feel like
感激吗？百分之百感激。因为我觉得
every time I have a low point and
每次我经历低谷、
struggle and go within rather than go
挣扎和内心挣扎时，我都会从中受益匪浅。 与其
without
放弃，
I develop an intimate relationship even
我不如
deeper with myself and I have a greater
与自己建立更深层次的亲密关系，我对自己的
level of trust and faith that not only
信任和信念也更强了，我相信
is everything figure outable but that
一切问题都能解决，而且
there is a a higher intelligence there
存在着更高的智慧，一种
is a greater wisdom that is absolutely
更伟大的力量，它绝对
on my side and that it has nothing to do
站在我这边，这
with external tools or external people
与外在的工具、人
or external expectations and then if I'm
或期望无关。如果我
quiet enough and courageous enough to be
足够安静、足够勇敢，能够
still the answers Within
静下心来，答案就会在我内心深处浮现。
the one I was thinking of uh was
我印象最深刻的一次是什么时候？嗯，
actually
其实是
Josh and I were sitting on the couch and
乔什和我坐在沙发上，
he told me I don't think I love you
他告诉我“我想我不再爱你了，
anymore I think this is done
我觉得我们结束了”。
and I
我当时
was in such shock this was remember we
震惊极了。记得我们之前
were talking about how there was like a
聊过
we've had many ups and downs but this
我们之间经历过很多起起落落，但这一次，
was one where we were sitting and I was
我们坐在一起，我
looking at him and I felt that his heart
看着他，感觉他的心完全封闭了。
was like so not available it wasn't just
那不是
a normal fight
普通的争吵，
and Stephen my gut dropped and I felt
斯蒂芬，我感觉心都凉了，
it was like all the oxygen got sucked
好像房间里的氧气都被抽走了。
and I felt like I had [__] up the best
我觉得我因为工作成瘾毁掉了
relationship that I had ever had with my
我人生中最美好的关系。
and I remember it was a moment of either
我记得当时我感到很
like feeling fearful like okay this is
害怕，不知道该怎么办。 事情已经
done and I need a defense mechanism
结束了，我需要一个防御机制，大概就是那种“
get out you know what I mean like fine
去你的，滚蛋”之类的，你知道我的意思吧，就像“好吧，
it's over
结束了”。
and then I said I remember saying he
然后我记得我说过，他说他
said I don't I don't think I love you
不爱我了，
anymore and I said that's not true
我说这不是真的，事情还没
it's like this is not over and but it
结束。但这
did not come from like it sounds super
并不是出于什么原因，听起来可能很
aggressive I know that that sounds
咄咄逼人，我知道这听起来
really scary but there was and I'm not
很可怕，但当时确实有这么一个声音，我不是在
kidding you there was this inner voice
开玩笑，我内心有个声音在说：
that I was like he's hurt you're hurt
他受伤了，你也受伤了，要为
fight for this relationship do not let
这段感情而战，不要
this go so that in her voice you know
放手。你知道，
it's easy especially for someone like me
这很容易，尤其像我这样的人，
when when I can get hurt like there's a
一旦受伤，就会有一种
somewhat of a natural or at least back
本能，或者至少
at that time to be defensive right and
在当时是这样，会想要防御，
say you know I don't love you I'm this
说：‘你知道，我不爱你了，我们结束了，
is done I'm walking out I don't need you
我要走了，我不需要你。’
and I was like you [__] be humble and
我就想，‘你他妈的要谦虚点，要
you fight for this relationship and I
为这段感情而战。’我
remember sitting there and telling him
记得我坐在那里告诉他，
that this wasn't over I understand that
事情还没结束，我知道
he believes he doesn't love me anymore I
他觉得他不爱我了，我
said I still love you more than anything
说我依然爱你，而且比什么都爱。” 任何事
and I'm willing to do whatever it takes
我都愿意做，我愿意付出一切努力去
to see if this can be repaired and I
看看这段关系是否还能修复。我
asked him I said I'm willing to do
问他，我说我愿意做
anything we can go to therapy we
任何事，我们可以去做心理咨询，什么都行，
whatever but are you willing to at least
但你愿意至少
take a step to see if it's possible
迈出一步，看看有没有可能吗？
because I think this is the greatest
因为我觉得这是
love of my life and I don't want to lose
我生命中最伟大的爱，我不想失去
you
你。我
I saw something in him crack meaning
看到他眼中闪过一丝裂痕，这意味着
that I could see he was hurt and he
我能看出他很受伤，他
didn't know I cared that much and I
不知道我这么在乎他。我
think it took me being so a little bit
想，正是那一刻我有点
aggressive but also really loving in
强势，但也充满爱意，我
that moment and saying I am willing to
说我愿意
fight for this and I don't want to lose
为这段关系而战，我不想失去
you and yeah I've probably been an
你。是的，我可能曾经是个
[__] but I'm willing to work on it
混蛋，但我愿意改正，
and I want to fix it and so it was that
我想修复这段关系。所以，我内心深处有个
inner voice that there was like [__] him
声音在说“去他的”，
like you know it was like leave whatever
你知道，就像“离开他”之类的，
but the deeper voice said fight for this
但那个更深沉的声音却说“为这段关系而战”。
and I'm so grateful that I listened to
我非常感激我听从了
that rather than the whiny egoic
那个声音，而不是那个自私自利、充满怨恨的
voice that was just you know hurt and
声音，你知道，那种声音只是让我感到受伤和被
felt rejected
拒绝。
Mary thank you
玛丽，谢谢你，
thank you for um
谢谢你，嗯，这
I mean it's so much I mean I could sit
意义重大，我真想坐在
here and talk to you for five hours
这里。 能和你聊五个小时，
around all of these topics because I
围绕这些话题，我
learned so much you've got such a
受益匪浅。你对
perspective on challenges that so many
许多
people are solving and these are all the
人正在努力解决的挑战有着独到的见解，而且你的经验丰富，见解深刻，不掺杂任何废话。这些都是
most important challenges that your book
你书《
everything is figureoutable is full of
一切皆可解决》（Everything Is Figureoutable）中探讨的最重要的挑战，书中充满了针对
challenges that I get every day that's
我每天都会遇到的这些挑战的解决方案。这就是
why I said to you before we started
为什么在录音之前我跟你说，要把
condense my notes on this conversation
这次谈话的内容精简成笔记真的很难，
because these are all the questions that
因为这些都是
I'm being asked and you've answered them
我经常被问到的问题，而你用
in an original a thoughtful and
一种原创的、深思熟虑的、
inexperienced based way from your own
基于自身经验的方式回答了它们，而
truth um not from something you've read
不是从你读到的东西
somewhere or from cliche that is so
或者陈词滥调中寻找答案。这一点非常
important and also time genius
重要，而且你真是个天才。
I mean your description of that
你对这个问题的描述，
people in my life I think maybe too many
我觉得它与我生活中很多人的经历都产生了共鸣，甚至可能太多了。
people in my life so it's wonderful that
所以，
you've got a resource out there that
你能够提供这样一个资源，让
everyone can access that I have no no
每个人都能获取，这真是太棒了。我毫不
doubt in my mind that they will
怀疑，它真的能够
help them go on that journey of finding
帮助人们踏上
out their true fulfilled self and
寻找真我、
aligning themselves a little bit better
实现自我价值的旅程。 稍微好一点，能更好地
against that external voice
对抗外界的声音，
um and a little bit closer to that
也稍微更接近
internal voice thank you for your time
内心的声音。感谢您抽出时间，
thank you for your wisdom your honesty
感谢您的智慧、坦诚、
your vulnerability and everything you're
脆弱，以及您
doing for so many people because it's
为这么多人所做的一切，因为这真的非常
really important and you know I think a
重要。你知道，我一直在思考
lot about the coaching space and it's
教练领域，这个领域，
heavily dominated especially at the top
尤其是在顶尖领域，几乎完全被男性主导。比如
um Tony Robbins you know you think you
托尼·罗宾斯，你知道，你会
think about all these individuals
想到所有这些人，
um and they don't have the same
但他们没有同样的
experience they don't have the same
经历，他们对身为女性的感受没有同样的
insight into
洞察力。女性也在
um go struggling with an external
与
narrative from from society that people
来自社会的外部叙事作斗争，而像
like me as a man would never really
我这样的男性永远无法真正
understand
理解。
but your work your work appeals to both
但您的工作，您的工作能同时吸引这两种人，这很
that's special so thank you thank you
特别。所以，非常感谢您抽出
for giving me your time thank you so
时间，
much for having me on it was an absolute
非常感谢您邀请我来，这绝对是一种
joy and an honor quick one as you might
荣幸和快乐。顺便提一下，您可能
know crafted are one of the sponsors of
知道，Crafted是这个播客的赞助商之一，
this podcast and crafted are a jewelry
Crafted是一个珠宝
brand and they make really meaningful
品牌，他们制作的珠宝非常有意义。
pieces of jewelry I think I've worn this
我想我戴这件
piece for almost a year it hasn't broken
首饰快一年了，它没有坏，也
hasn't changed color because it's really
没有变色。 它的
really good quality and it costs roughly
质量真的非常好，价格大概
50 Quid I'm not the type of person that
50英镑。我不是那种
has Rolexes or jewelry that cost tens of
拥有劳力士或者价值数万
thousands of pounds I want pieces that
英镑珠宝的人，我想要的是
are reliable that look beautiful and
可靠、美观，并且
that holds meaning and significance for
对我来说有意义和价值的饰品。这正是
me and that's exactly why I've worn
我一直以来佩戴
crafted for so long and when we have the
Crafted饰品的原因。当我们
conversation about them sponsoring this
谈到他们赞助这个
podcast I was so unbelievably Keen for
播客时，我非常渴望
them to do so check it out if you're a
他们能这样做。如果你是
guy crafted london.com and yeah if you
男士，可以去看看craftedlondon.com。对了，如果你
get any pieces of crafted tag man let me
买了任何Crafted Tag Man的饰品，请
know what you think
告诉我你的想法。
[Music]
[音乐]